<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE PLAY SYSTEM "play.dtd">
<PLAY>
	<TITLE></TITLE>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>F O R  Y O U R  C O N S I D E R AT I O N</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>UNKNOWN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE></LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BEST ADAPTED SCREENPLAY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>F O R  Y O U R  C O N S I D E R AT I O N</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Christopher Markus & Stephen McFeely     AVENGERS: ENDGAME  Adapted Screenplay Written by Christopher Markus and Stephen McFeely</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>LILA BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BEST ADAPTED SCREENPLAY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Why three?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>LILA BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>‘Cause two’s not enough and four’s too much-  LAURA BARTON (O.S.) You guys want mustard or mayo, or both?  CLINT TURNS.  IN THE FIELD BEHIND THEM, his wife, LAURA BARTON sets up a picnic as COOPER and NATHANIEL play soccer.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>LILA BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Who puts mayo on a hot dog?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>LILA BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’ll both have mustard, hon! (to Lila) Okay.  Draw back, deep breath...  She lets loose.  THUD!  HER ARROW HITS NEAR THE BULLS-EYE.  CLINT BARTON (CONT'D) Good job, Hawkeye.  Go get your arrow.  LAURA BARTON (O.S.) Enough murder practice!  Soup’s on!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>One sec, babe.  Be right there! We’re gonna kill some hot dogs. We’re hungry.  But when he turns back...LILA IS GONE.  The bow and arrow lie at his feet.  He stares.   2  CLINT BARTON (CONT'D) Lila?  Babe, did you see Lila-  He turns to his wife, BUT SHE’S GONE.  So are the boys.  The soccer ball rolls to a stop near the picnic blanket.  NO ONE CAN BE SEEN FOR A HUNDRED YARDS IN ALL DIRECTIONS.  CLINT BARTON (CONT'D) Guys?  Guys, come on...  Clint walks toward the field, dread growing.  CLINT BARTON (CONT'D) Laura?  Clint breaks into a panicked run.  CLINT BARTON (CONT'D) LAURA!  CLINT MELTS DOWN, SPINNING AROUND, FRANTIC...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MARVEL FLIP</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE></LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MARVEL FLIP</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(offering his hand) Good sport.  Have fun?  Nebula studies his hand, confused.  Finally she shakes.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It was fun.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>This thing on?  Hey, Ms. Potts. Pep.  If you find this recording, don’t post it on social media. It’s going to be a real tearjerker.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Pep, I know I said no more surprises.  But, I gotta say, I was really hoping to pull off one last one.  But it looks like...well, you know what it looks like.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t feel bad about this.  I mean, actually, if you grovel for a couple weeks, and then move on with enormous guilt...I should probably lie down for a minute, rest my eyes.  Please know, when I drift off, it will be like every day lately.  I’m fine, totally fine. I’m going to dream about you.  It’s always you.  Tony switches the helmet off.  TIME CUT:  NEBULA finds TONY SPRAWLED ON THE FLOOR.  TIME CUT:  4   5  Nebula helps Tony into Quill’s chair.  Tony slumps, completely still.  Nebula gives him his privacy.  Move in on Tony’s face as...A LIGHT SLOWLY GROWS BRIGHTER. Soon, the entire flight deck glows as bright as a sun.  Nebula appears from the galley, shading her eyes.  Tony’s eyelids flutter.  Finally, he opens them to see...  CAPTAIN MARVEL (CAROL DANVERS) hovering in space.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I couldn’t stop him.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Neither could we.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I lost the kid.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(unable to say it all) We...lost...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Is Pepper...?  5   6  JUST THEN, PEPPER POTTS THROWS HERSELF INTO TONY’S ARMS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Stay here, you stay right here-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m not going anywhere.  NEARBY, NEBULA watches the sad humans.  ROCKET SITS BESIDE HER, GRATEFUL.  She rests a hand on his furry head.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s been twenty-three days since Thanos came to Earth.  TONY, weak, sits in a hi-tech wheelchair, IV dripping into his arm.  He stares, taking in the loss:  SAM WILSON.  SECRETARY ROSS.  SHARON CARTER.  SCOTT LANG. HOPE VAN DYNE.  HANK PYM.  NICK FURY.  At Fury, Carol bites back emotion.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>World governments are in pieces, as you can imagine.  But the parts that still work are trying to take a census.  It looks like he did what he said he was going to do.  JANE FOSTER.  ERIK SELVIG.  WONG.  DR. STRANGE.  THE BARTON FAMILY.  QUILL.  DRAX.  MANTIS.  GROOT.  PETER PARKER.  Finally, Tony looks away.  RHODEY turns it off.  NATASHA (CONT'D) Thanos wiped out fifty percent of all the living creatures on Earth.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not just Earth.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You sure about that?  6   7</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You never have to ask me that.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where is he now?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We don’t know.  He just opened a portal and walked through.  Tony looks out to see...THOR on the patio.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What’s his deal?  ROCKET (O.S.) He’s pissed.  Tony turns to see Rocket for the first time.  ROCKET (CONT'D) He thinks he failed.  Which, of course, he did.  But there’s a lot of that going around, ain’t there?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Until this second, I literally thought you were a Build-a-Bear.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’ve been hunting Thanos for three weeks - deep space scans, satellites - we got nothing.  Tony, you fought him-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Who told you that?  I didn’t fight him, he wiped my face with a planet while a Bleecker Street magician gave away the store.  There was no fight because he’s not beatable.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Did he give you anything to go on? Clues, coordinates-  Tony stares, lost, barely acknowledging Steve.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I saw this coming, few years back. Didn’t wanna believe.  I thought I was dreaming...  7   8</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, I need you to focus-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And I needed you, as in past tense. That trumps what you need.  It’s too late, buddy.  You know what I need?  Tony turns to everyone, slightly unstable.  TONY (CONT'D) I need a shave and a burger, not a bowl of soup. (stands) And I believe I remember telling all of you, alive and otherwise, that we needed a suit of armor around the world, whether it impacted our precious freedoms or not-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But that didn’t work out, did it?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I said we’d lose, you said we’d “do that together, too.”  Guess what, Cap, we lost, and you weren’t there.  But that’s what we do, right?  Our best work after the fact?  We’re the “Avengers”, not the “Pre-vengers-”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, take it easy...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’ve got nothing for ya, Cap.  No coordinates, no clues, no strategies, no options.  Zero, zip, nada.  No trust. (rips out RT) Here.  You take this.  You find him, you put this on, and hide. (drops to his knees) I’m fine!  Tony COLLAPSES.  Rhodey catches him.  8   9</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Bruce gave him a sedative.  Should be out the rest of the day.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(heading for the lab) Take care of him.  When I come back, I’ll bring a bottle of Xorrian elixir.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where are you going?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>To kill Thanos.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, hey, hang on.  We’re sort of a team here.  Between you and me, morale’s a little fragile.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, I’m sorry.  My fault.  Carol sees Steve and Rhodey catch up.  She claps her hands.  CAROL DANVERS (CONT'D) All right, team!  I’m going to go kill Thanos.  Message me if you get any intel that can help. Otherwise, I’ll report back when he’s dead.  Great work, everybody.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Look, we realize “up there’s” more your territory, but this is our fight, too.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Do you even know where he is?  9   10</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I know people who might-  NEBULA (O.S.) Don’t bother.  They all turn to see NEBULA in THE LIVING AREA DOORWAY.  NEBULA (CONT'D) I can tell you where Thanos is.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thanos spent a long time trying to...perfect me.  When he worked, he talked.  About his Great Plan. Even disassembled, I wanted to please him.  I’d ask, where would we go once his plan was complete? His answer was always the same: “To the Garden.”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re saying Thanos had a retirement plan.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where’s this garden?  ROCKET brings up EARTH on A HOLO-MAP.  A BRIGHT SURGE OF ENERGY ENVELOPS THE PLANET (EMANATING FROM WAKANDA).</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>When Thanos snapped his fingers, Earth become ground zero for a power surge of ridiculously cosmic proportions.  No one’s seen anything like it.  He shifts the map, crossing billions of light years, to...AN IDENTICAL SURGE ENVELOPING A MYSTERIOUS, ORANGE PLANET.  ROCKET (CONT'D) Until two days ago.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re saying he snapped his fingers again.  Where?  10   11  Rocket zooms the holo-image toward a cluster of stars...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Planet is unnamed, but inhabitable. Rich atmosphere, good soil-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>A garden.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BRUCE BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thanos is there.  And he just used the stones.  Steve eyes everyone.  THOR FINALLY LOOKS UP.  BRUCE BANNER (CONT'D) (thinking of himself) You know, we’d be going short- handed.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BRUCE BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Because he killed all our friends.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Are we saying they’re dead?  We’re using that word now?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He’s still got the stones.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, we take them.  And we use them to bring everybody back.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BRUCE BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Just like that?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BRUCE BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  Just like that.  No one speaks.  Finally...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>If there’s even the smallest chance we can undo this, then we owe it to everyone who’s not sitting here to try.  Everyone looks around the room...AGREED.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BRUCE BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>If we do this...why would it end any differently than it did before?  11   12</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BRUCE BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Because before you didn’t have me.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, new girl.  All of us in here are about that superhero life. Where’ve you been all this time?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>There’s a lot of people in the universe.  And they didn’t all have you.  THOR STANDS.  He crosses to Carol and holds out his hand. STORMBREAKER WHIPS PAST HER HEAD, RUFFLING HER HAIR.  Carol doesn’t flinch.  Thor smiles.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I like this one.  Steve stares at the planet a long, deciding moment.  Then...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Let’s go get that son of a bitch.  SLAM TO: TITLE: “AVENGERS: ENDGAME”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Trust me.  You get used to it.  ROCKET looks around from the pilot’s chair.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, who here hasn’t been to space?  STEVE, NATASHA, and RHODEY half-raise their hands.  ROCKET (CONT'D) Oh, you’re gonna hate this.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Approaching jump in three, two...  STEVE’S FINGERS TIGHTEN on the arm rest as...  12   13</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’ll head down for recon.  If I’m not back in fifteen, you’ll know I found him.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>This is going to work, Steve.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I know it will. (beat) Because I don’t know what I’m going to do if it doesn’t.  JUST THEN, CAROL FLIES UP TO THE OTHER SIDE OF THE GLASS.  CAROL DANVERS (OVER COM) No satellites, no ships, no armies. No ground defenses of any kind. It’s just him.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s enough.  The Avengers exchange a look.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where are they?  Thanos doesn’t answer.  CAROL PRESSES HIM TO HIS KNEES.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Answer the question!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>The universe required correction. After that, the stones served no purpose beyond temptation.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BRUCE BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You murdered trillions.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BRUCE BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You should be grateful.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where are the stones?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Gone.  Reduced to atoms.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BRUCE BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You used them two days ago!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BRUCE BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I used the stones to destroy the stones.  It nearly killed me. But the work is done.  It always will be.  That lands, sickening.  ROCKET SEARCHES, FRANTIC, NEAR TEARS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No...they can’t be gone...  14   15</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He’s lying.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>My father is many things.  A liar is not one of them.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you, daughter.  Perhaps I’ve treated you-  SWOOSH.  THOR’S AXE SEVERS THANOS’ HEAD FROM HIS BODY.  IT HITS THE FLOOR, FOLLOWED BY THE THUD OF HIS HUGE FRAME.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What did you do?  Thor just stares, his long journey a failure.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I went for the head.  As Thor walks away, Steve looks at Thanos’ head on the ground.  IT’S OVER.  THEY LOST.  FADE TO BLACK.  OVER BLACK: “FIVE YEARS LATER.”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GRIEVING MAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, I went on a date the other day.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>JIMMY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GRIEVING MAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good job, Bobby.  Back in the game.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GRIEVING MAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>JIMMY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you, Jimmy. (to the group) First in five years.  I sat there at dinner thinking, what are we even supposed to talk about?  STEVE ROGERS, thinner, older, LISTENS INTENTLY.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GRIEVING MAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What did you talk about?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GRIEVING MAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Same old crap.  How much things have changed.  How much we miss the Mets.  My job, his job.  Then it got kind of quiet.  He cried during the salads.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLDER MAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GRIEVING MAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What about you?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GRIEVING MAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLDER MAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I cried just before dessert.  But I’m seeing him again tomorrow. So...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GRIEVING MAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s great.  You’ve already done the hardest part.  You took a jump, didn’t know where you’d come down. And that’s it, those little brave baby steps we’ve gotta take.  To try to make us feel whole again, to find a purpose... (to everyone) I went into the ice right after I met the love of my life.  Woke up seventy years later and...had to keep going.  The group takes this in.  16   17  STEVE (CONT'D) The world’s been left in our hands. If we don’t do something with it...then Thanos might as well have killed all of us.  People nod, but Steve seems unconvinced by his own words.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hello?  He hears A CLACKING.  A KID on a bicycle rides by, playing card wedged between his spokes.  Scott waves him down.  The kid stops.  17   18  SCOTT LANG (CONT'D) Hey.  Kid.  What happened here?  The kid says nothing.  He just stares at Scott with a haunted look.  Then he stands on his pedal and keeps riding.  CLACK-CLACK-CLACK-CLACK-CLACK-CLACK-CLACK...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What? (realizing) Cassie...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Cassie!  Cassie!  SOON, A TEEN GIRL opens the door, shocked.  A very long beat.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CASSIE LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Dad?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CASSIE LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Peanut?  Scott wraps his arms around CASSIE LANG (14), now five years older than when he last saw her.  She hugs him, CRYING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CASSIE LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I thought you were gone.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CASSIE LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m sorry.  I’m back...I’m back...I’m back...  18   19</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And?  NEBULA (HOLO) It was an infectious garbage scow.  ROCKET (HOLO) So thanks for the hot tip-  CAROL DANVERS (HOLO) You were closer.  ROCKET (HOLO) And now we smell like garbage-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(to Okoye) You get a reading on those tremors?  OKOYE (HOLO) Minor subduction in the African plate.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Do we have a visual?  How are you handling it?  OKOYE (HOLO) Nat.  It was a mild earthquake.  In the ocean.  We handle it by not handling it.  Natasha looks burdened.  Rhodey steps in.  19   (MORE)  20  RHODEY (HOLO) I can have NASA redirect a satellite, do a sweep just to make sure.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thanks.  Carol, you’re still coming our way next month?  CAROL DANVERS (HOLO) Not likely.  ROCKET (HOLO) Getting another haircut?  CAROL DANVERS (HOLO) Listen, fur-face, I’m covering a lot of territory out here.  The things that have been happening on Earth have been happening everywhere else.  On thousands of planets.  You might not see me for a long time.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>All right.  Everybody keep keeping their eyes open.  This channel’s always active.  Anything goes sideways, anyone makes trouble where they shouldn’t, it comes through me.  They ad lib their goodbyes as they sign off, except Rhodey.  NATASHA (CONT'D) What’s up?  Where are you?  RHODEY (HOLO) Mexico.  Got some news.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Federalés found a room full of bodies outside Juarez.  Cartel guys.  Guns still in their pants.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Could be a rival hit-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But it wasn’t.  Same MO as Marseille.  And Kiev. (MORE)  20   RHODEY (CONT'D)  21  (beat) It’s definitely Barton.  She nods, grim, reluctantly accepting.  RHODEY (CONT'D) What he’s done here...what he’s been doing...I got to tell you, part of me doesn’t want to find him.  Natasha just stares a long beat.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Find out where’s he going next.  Rhodey nods, signing off.  Natasha sits there, THEN CRUMPLES.  After a long beat...  STEVE (O.S.) I’d offer to cook you dinner but you seem sad enough already.  Natasha turns to see STEVE in the doorway.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Come by to do your laundry?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And see a friend.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Your friend’s fine.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>She leave the house today?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Nothing out there I particularly want to see.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I spotted a pod of whales coming over the bridge.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(dubious) In the Hudson.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Fewer ships, cleaner water.  Just saying, there’s still a world out there.  RHODEY (CONT'D)  21   22</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>If you’re about to tell me to look on the bright side, I’m about to hit you with a peanut butter sandwich.  Steve relents, LETTING DOWN HIS FACADE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sorry.  Force of habit.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t know how you do it.  Steve bites into the uneaten half of her sandwich.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I guess I don’t know how not to.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Me, neither.  After a long moment, Steve looks up at her, honest.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I keep telling them, move on.  Grow past it.  And some of them actually do.  But not us.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>If I move on, who does this?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Maybe it doesn’t need to be done.  Natasha takes that in.  Steve is thinking of giving up.  She looks around at Avengers Compound.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I used to have nothing.  Then I got this.  This job, this family.  And I was better because of it.  She chokes slightly, collecting herself.  NATASHA (CONT'D) And even though they’re gone, I’m still trying to be...better.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I think we both need to get a life.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You first.  22   23  They stare at each other a long, melancholy moment.  THEN, WE HEAR A PING.  NATASHA SWIPES TO A CCTV DISPLAY: SCOTT LANG’S FACE FILLS A SCREEN, LUIS’ VAN BEHIND HIM.  SCOTT LANG (ON SCREEN) Hello?  Is anyone home?  This is, uh, Scott Lang?  We met a few years ago.  At the airport?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>This an old message?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(stunned) It’s the front gate.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What?  Yes.  He turns to STEVE and NATASHA.  SCOTT LANG (CONT'D) Have either of you guys ever studied quantum physics?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Only to make conversation.  Steve glances at her.  She shrugs.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Well, five years ago, just before this Thanos guy...I went into a place called the Quantum Realm. It’s like its own microscopic universe.  You can only get there if you’re incredibly small.  Hope, she’s my...she was supposed to pull me out.  But then Thanos happened. And I was stuck in there.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m sorry.  It must’ve been a long five years.  23   24</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(getting excited) Okay, but that’s the thing.  It wasn’t.  For me, it was only five hours.  The rules in the Quantum Realm aren’t like out here. They’re completely unpredictable. Is anybody gonna eat that sandwich?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Scott, what are you talking about?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Time works differently in the Quantum Realm.  Steve and Natasha share a look.  SCOTT LANG (CONT'D) Problem is, right now, it’s chaos, there’s no way to navigate it.  But what if we could figure out a way to enter the Quantum Realm at a certain point in time...and come out in another.  Like, before Thanos-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wait...wait.  Scott.  Are you talking about a time machine?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, not a machine.  More like a... (searches, then gives up) Yeah, like a time machine.  I know it sounds crazy...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Scott, I get emails from a raccoon. Nothing’s crazy anymore.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, who do we talk to about this?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Morgan H. Stark.  Chow time.  Want some lunch?  Silence.  Then MORGAN STARK (4) steps out of her play tent, wearing A PURPLE-BLUE IRON MAN HELMET (RESCUE).</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Define lunch or be disintegrated.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You should not be wearing that. It’s part of a special anniversary gift I made for Mom.  You thinking about lunch?  Tony gently takes the helmet off, revealing A YOUNG GIRL.  TONY (CONT'D) Where’d you find this?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Garage.  Tony picks her up, walking toward the house.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You like going in the garage?  So does Daddy.  It’s all right.  Mommy never wears what I buy her.  TIME CUT:  Tony and Morgan exit the woods.  Suddenly, Tony stops.  In the driveway, STEVE ROGERS stares at him.  NATASHA AND SCOTT GET OUT OF THE CAR BEHIND HIM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I just want to thank you folks for dropping by.  It’s not every day one gets to contemplate biting it on an inter-dimensional timescape.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’ve got some objections to the plan.  25   26</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So you’re calling it a plan.  To me, it sounds like an exotic suicide method.  Not to mention, it’s impossible.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We know what it sounds like.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, after what you’ve seen, is anything really impossible?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Quantum fluctuation kinda messes with the Planck Scale, which then triggers the Deutsch Proposition, can we agree on that? (offering more tea) Chai? (back on message) In layman’s terms, it means you can cancel your Netflix subscription because you’re not coming home.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I did.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Which was a billion-to-one cosmic fluke.  Now you want to pull a- What are you calling it?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>A time heist.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, of course, a time heist, why didn’t we think of this before? Right, because it’s a pipe dream. Who are you again?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Still Scott...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, the Stones exist in the past. We could get them and bring them here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We can snap our own fingers.  We can bring everybody back.  26   27</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Or screw it up worse than he already has.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t believe we would.  Tony stares at Steve, a lot of water under the bridge.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Gotta say it.  Sometimes I’ve missed that giddy optimism.  Sadly, all your high hopes won’t help me if there’s no logical, tangible way for me to safely execute said “time heist.”  I believe the most likely outcome would be our collective demise.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not if we strictly follow the rules of time travel.  No talking to our past selves.  No betting on sporting events-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Stop, Scott.  Stop.  Are you telling me that your plan to save the universe is more than loosely based on Back to the Future?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(meaning “yes”) No...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good.  Because that would be horseshit.  Scientifically speaking, your brother’s picture doesn’t disappear just ‘cause you went to the dance with your mom. That’s not how quantum physics works.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We have to take a stand.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We did stand.  And yet here we are.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Look, Stark-  Can I call you Tony?  27   28</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Please don’t-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Fine.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I get that you’ve got a lot on the line, here.  You’ve got a wife.  A daughter.  But I lost someone very important - a lot of us did - and now we have a chance to save her, and everyone else, and you won’t even-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, Scott.  I won’t.  Even.  Suddenly, MORGAN walks onto the porch.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Mommy told me to come save you.  Tony takes Morgan into his arms and heads inside.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good job.  I’m saved. (to Steve) I wish you were coming here to ask me something else.  I’m honestly happy to see you.  If you want to stay-  Steve tries one last time.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, I get it.  And I’m happy for you.  I am.  But this is a second chance.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, well, I got my second chance right here.  I can’t roll the dice on it.  The table is set for six. If you don’t talk shop, you’re welcome to stay for lunch.  He exits.  28   29</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He’s scared.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He’s not wrong.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What are we gonna do?  We need him. You want to stop?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  I want to do it right. (beat) We’re going to need a really big brain.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Bigger than his?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>These are confusing times.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, that’s not what I’m-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m kidding, I get it.  It’s crazy. I wear shirts now!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But why?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Five years ago, we got our asses kicked, right?  29  ---   30  Smart Hulk eats a stack of pancakes in two bites.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He’s heard.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It was worse for me.  Because I lost twice.  First Hulk lost.  Then Banner lost.  Then we all lost.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No one blamed you, Bruce.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I did-  I feel like I’m the only one eating.  Here, try some.  He holds out a pizza.  They decline.  He shrugs.  SMART HULK (CONT'D) Thing is, I kept thinking, it didn’t have to be that way.  That the best of Banner and best of Hulk, if they’d worked together, maybe they could’ve stopped Thanos.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay.  But how did...this happen?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>For years I treated the Hulk like a disease, something to get rid of. But when I started treating him like the cure...  Smart Hulk MESHES HIS FINGERS together.  SMART HULK (CONT'D) Eighteen months in the Gamma Lab. I put the brains and the brawn together.  And now look at me. Best of both worlds.  TWO KIDS amble up to the booth.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>KID</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Mr. Hulk?  Can we get a picture?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>KID</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>100%, little lady.  The kid hands a phone to Steve.  SMART HULK makes a duck face as Steve sheepishly snaps the pic, handing the phone back.  30   31  SMART HULK (CONT'D) (to the fan) Thanks, pal.  Hulk out!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, Bruce, about what we said-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>The time travel do-over?  I don’t know, that’s kind of outside my field of expertise...  Natasha nods at his Smart Hulk-ness, history between them.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You pulled this off.  I remember a time that was impossible, too.  He considers, then finally relents, pulling out his phone.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m supposed to be on Oprah next week, but I guess I could move things around.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Friday, you up?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIDAY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yes, sir.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIDAY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’ve had a mild inspiration, like to see if it checks out.  I would like to run one last sim before we pack it in for the night.  This time, in the shape of a Mobius Strip, inverted.  31   32</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIDAY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Processing.  The model forms.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIDAY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>All right, give me the eigenvalue of that particle, factoring in spectral decomp.  Run it.  That’ll take a second.  And don’t worry if it doesn’t pan out, I’m just kind of...  THE CAPACITOR GLOWS.  A HOLO-MAN DRIFTS INTO A CIRCULAR WORMHOLE, LOOPING...RETURNING TO THE PLACE IT FIRST LEFT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIDAY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Model rendered.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIDAY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(in awe) Shit.  MORGAN STARK (O.S.) Shit.  Tony turns to see HIS DAUGHTER in the doorway.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What are you doing up?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Shit.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>First of all, that’s a Mommy word, she coined it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Why are you up?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I just had something on my mind.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Was it juice pops?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Correct.  Great minds think alike. What kind do you want?  32   33</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You done? (finishing her popsicle) Now you are.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tell me a story.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Once upon a time, Maguna went to bed.  The end.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That was a bad story.  He runs his hand over her hair.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Love you tons.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Love you three thousand.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wow, that’s a lot.  Tony turns out the light, exits.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s up there.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What’re you reading?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>A book about composting-  33   34</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I think I solved it.  Pepper looks up.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Just so we’re both talking about the same thing-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Time travel.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s amazing.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And terrifying.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>To say the least.  He sits beside her.  She stares, SHARING IN HIS DILEMMA.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We got really lucky-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I know-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not everybody did.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I can’t help everybody.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Except, it sort of seems like you can.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not if I stopped right here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, trying to get you to stop is one of the few failures of my life.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I could just lock the lab, put it in a trunk, sink it to the bottom of the lake, and go to bed.  34   35</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But could you rest?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re sure these modifications are safe?  He looks over to...SMART HULK, WEARING READING GLASSES, MAKING ADJUSTMENTS TO A NEW CONTROL PANEL.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I reran my calculations three times-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Because the guy who invented this thing is pretty much a genius-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I have seven PhD’s, an MD, the Hans Bethe Award for Physics, and I’m personal friends with Bill Nye the Science Guy.  We’re good.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  And you look like that on purpose.  STEVE and NATASHA enter from outside.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Breakers are set, emergency generator’s on stand-by.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good.  If we blow the grid, I don’t want to lose Tiny back in the ‘50’s.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Excuse me?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He was kidding.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I was kidding.  35   36</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(to Hulk) You were kidding, right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Honestly, I have no idea.  We’re attempting time travel.  Either it’s all a joke, or none of it is. (loudly to Scott) We’re good!  Helmet on.  Scott puts on his helmet, slightly dubious.  SMART HULK (CONT'D) Okay.  I’m going to send you back one week, give you an hour to look around, then bring you back in ten seconds.  Make sense?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Perfectly not confusing.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good luck, Scott.  You’ve got this.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(inspired) Yes, I do, Captain America.  Yes, I-  SMART HULK PULLS A LEVER.  SCOTT SHRINKS TO NOTHING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Counting down from three, two, one...  SUDDENLY SCOTT REAPPEARS...BUT HE’S 12-YEARS-OLD.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Uh, guys?  This doesn’t feel right.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Is that Scott?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Probably...?  He scrambles, hitting buttons.  SCOTT SHRINKS TO NOTHING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Get him back!  Smart Hulk flips a switch.  SCOTT REAPPEARS...AT AGE 93.  36   37</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, my back!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Bruce!  Get it under control.  What the hell is going on?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I got it, I know exactly what’s going on.  Pretty much.  SCOTT SHRINKS TO NOTHING AGAIN.  HULK TYPES FRANTICALLY with A PENCIL, fingers too big for the keys.  2-YEAR OLD SCOTT APPEARS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, my God.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s a baby.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s Scott.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>As a baby!  Smart Hulk hits a button.  Baby Scott disappears.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>When I tell you, kill the power! (throwing a switch) Now!  NATASHA KILLS THE POWER.  Normal Scott stumbles off the pad.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Somebody peed my pants.  I don’t know if it was baby-me or old-me. Or just me-me.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Why the long face?  Wild guess, he turned into a baby?  37   38</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Among other things.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(getting out of the car) EPR Paradox.  Instead of pushing Lang through time, you were pushing time through Lang.  It’s dangerous. I probably should’ve cautioned you against it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You did.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank god, I’m here.  Regardless, I fixed it.  He holds up...HIS STAR-SHAPED CAPACITOR.  TONY (CONT'D) That is a fully-functioning, time- space GPS.  I just want peace. Resentment is corrosive.  I hate it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Me, too.  Something eases between them, for the first time in years.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’ve got a shot at the Stones.  I just need you to know my priorities.  Bring back everyone we lost, hopefully.  Keep what I found, definitely.  And, let’s not die trying.  Steve looks at Tony.  Finally, he offers his hand.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sounds like a deal.  They shake.  This is a long time coming.  Finally...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But wait, there’s more.   Act now, and it comes with a bonus offer.  Tony pops the trunk.  Steve stares, moved, at...HIS SHIELD.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, I don’t know-  38   39</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What’s to know?  He made it for you.  Plus, I gotta get it out of the garage before Morgan takes it sledding.  Steve finally picks up the shield, SLIDING IT ONTO HIS ARM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you, Tony.  Tony chokes up, then covers by slamming the trunk.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Just don’t flaunt it.  I didn’t bring enough for the whole team. We are getting the whole team, right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’re trying.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, Humie.  Where’s Big Green?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Um, kitchen, I think.  Scott tries a smile at Nebula.  She just hits her COM:  NEBULA (INTO COM) Rhodey, careful on re-entry. There’s an idiot in the landing zone.  She goes in.  THEN, WHAM, WAR MACHINE LANDS, STARTLING SCOTT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, my God!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What’s up, Regular-Sized Man?  Rhodey goes inside as SMART HULK walks out, carrying an overnight bag.  He hands Scott some tacos.  39   40</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Finally.  I ain’t got all day.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I call shotgun!  As he walks up the Benatar’s gangway, PRE-LAP A METALLIC SCRAPING SOUND.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What the heck are they looking at?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m kind of famous...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, I’m sure that’s it.  Kind of a step down from golden palaces and magic hammers...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>They lost Asgard, then half their people.  Maybe they’re just happy to have a home.  VALKYRIE (O.S.) You shouldn’t have come.  VALKYRIE approaches from the pier.  Smart Hulk GRINS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, Valkyrie!  Great to see you!  He goes for a hug...VAL DOESN’T.  She studies the new him.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Uh huh.  I liked you better either of the other ways.  40   41</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>This is Rocket.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey. (to both) He won’t see you.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We didn’t say we were here to see-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Great, then you can hose out the gut buckets-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’re definitely here to see him.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He can’t give you what you need.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s that bad?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We only see him once a month.  When he comes in for “supplies.”  She nods to A DOZEN BEER KEGS STACKED OUTSIDE A PUB.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Something died in here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hello...?  Thor...?  THOR (O.S.) Are you here about the cable?  We hear a HEAVY SHUFFLING as someone approaches.  41   42  THOR (CONT'D) Cinemax went out two days ago, and the sports are all...fuzzy...  THOR enters, CONFUSED, A LITTLE DRUNK, SHIRTLESS...AND TREMENDOUSLY FAT.  Rocket and Hulk stare.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thor?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>BROS!  Bring it in!  Thor hugs Smart Hulk.  He turns to Rocket, who steps back.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, I’m good.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hulk, you know my boys, Korg and Miek, right?  KORG and MIEK sit on the couch, playing Playstation 4.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>KORG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Beer’s in the bucket.  Feel free to log on to the WiFi.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>KORG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, guys.  Long time no-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>KORG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thor!  This kid on the TV just called me a dickhead!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>KORG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Noobmaster again?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>KORG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>NoobMaster69 called me a dickhead-  Thor snatches KORG’S HEADSET and hisses into the mic.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>KORG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Noobmaster, this is Thor, again. God of Thunder.  This is your last warning.  Log off this game or I will come to your basement, rip off your arms and shove them up your butt. (handing the headset back) Right, who wants a drink?  42   (MORE)  43  SMART HULK AND ROCKET JUST STARE.  Thor pulls a beer from the fridge, and whacks the cap against STORMBREAKER.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, buddy, are you all right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t I look all right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(under his breath) You look like melted ice cream-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, what’s up?  Just here for a hang?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We need your help.  There’s a chance we can fix everything.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Like the cable?  It’s driving me bananas.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Like Thanos.  THOR GRABS HULK’S SHIRT, INTENSE.  KORG RISES FROM THE COUCH.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t say that name.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>KORG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, we don’t say that name in here.  Smart Hulk looks down at THOR’S HAND STILL ON HIS SHIRT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>KORG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Please take your hand off me.  Thor looks into Hulk’s eyes...and gently removes his hand.  SMART HULK (CONT'D) Now, I know the thought of...that guy might scare you-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Scared?  Why would I be scared of that guy?  I’m the one who killed that guy, remember? (looking around) Anyone else here kill that guy? (MORE)  43   THOR (CONT'D)  44  Didn’t think so.  Korg, tell everyone who chopped Thanos’ head off.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>KORG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Stormbreaker?  Thor uncaps a whiskey bottle.  BLAM, IT SHATTERS IN HIS HAND. Reveal...ROCKET, BLASTER SMOKING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>KORG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not.  Cool.  Man.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t.  Care.  Dude.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Look, I get it.  You’re in a rough patch.  I’ve been there.  But you know who helped me out of it?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Was it Natasha?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It was you.  You helped me.  And I need you to help me again.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Ask the Asgardians down there how much “my help” is worth.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>At least they’re alive-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>They were gods!  Now they’re fisherpeople! (sagging into a chair) The ones that are left, anyway.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s the thing.  I think we can bring them back.  Thor’s tempted, but shakes his head.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Stop.  Stop.  I know you think I’m down here, wallowing in my own self- pity, waiting to be rescued.  But I’m fine.  I’m happy.  Whatever it is you’re offering, don’t care. Couldn’t care less.  THOR (CONT'D)  44   45  Hulk and Rocket stare at Thor.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Come on, pal.  We need you.  He still can’t meet their gaze.  Finally...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>There’s beer in the ship.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(beat) What kind?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>AKIHIKO</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(Japanese, subtitled) Why are you doing this?  We never did anything to you!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RONIN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>AKIHIKO</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(Japanese, subtitled) You survived.  Half the planet didn’t.  They got Thanos.  You get me.  Akihiko attacks.  Ronin slashes him across the middle.  RONIN (CONT'D) (Japanese, subtitled) You’re done hurting people.  Akihiko gestures at the bodies in the street.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>AKIHIKO</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RONIN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We hurt people?  You’re crazy.  Ronin slashes Akihiko’s throat.  The man drops to his knees.  AKIHIKO (CONT'D) Wait!  Help me!  I’ll give you anything!  What do you want?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RONIN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>AKIHIKO</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What I want...you can’t give me.  Ronin finishes him off.  AKIHIKO GOES STILL.  SIRENS WAIL. Ronin removes his mask, revealing...  CLINT BARTON, haggard.  He hears A FOOTFALL.  He whirls, katana raised...then stops.  His face goes slack as...  NATASHA STEPS INTO A POOL OF LIGHT, A LARGE BLACK UMBRELLA KEEPING HER FROM THE RAIN.  They stare at each other.  Clint hasn’t seen her in years. She hasn’t seen what he’s become.  46  --   47</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RONIN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You shouldn’t be here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Neither should you.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’ve got a job to do.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That what you’re calling this?  She moves even closer.  He stiffens.  NATASHA (CONT'D) Killing these people isn’t going to bring your family back. (beat) We found something.  A chance, maybe...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t what?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Give me hope.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m just sorry I couldn’t give it sooner.  CLINT DISSOLVES, sagging into her arms.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And you’re only in there because you have tiny hands.  ROCKET, COVERED IN GREASE, WRIGGLES OUT A HATCH.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Fixed it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Get used to saying that.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Time travel suit, I like it.  SMART HULK awkwardly tries to fit a pair of RED TEST TUBES INTO THE TIME SUIT’S BELT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Easy, easy.  Careful with those.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m being very careful-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re being very Hulky-  Scott takes the tubes from him and inserts them, himself.  SCOTT LANG (CONT'D) These are Pym Particles.  You can’t shrink to the Quantum Realm without them, and since Hank Pym got snapped out of existence, we can’t make any more.  I told you.  We’ve only got enough for one round trip each, no do-overs.  Scott gently clicks the tubes into their housing.  SCOTT LANG (CONT'D) Plus two test runs-  SUDDENLY, SCOTT SHRINKS INTO NOTHING, THEN GROWS BACK.  He takes that in...  48   49  SCOTT LANG (CONT'D) One test run. (embarrassed) Okay, maybe I’m not ready.  CLINT BARTON (O.S.) I’m game.  They turn to see CLINT leaning in the doorway.  CLINT BARTON (CONT'D) I’ll do it.  TIME CUT:  NOW, CLINT WEARS THE TIME SUIT.  Scott looks on, sulky. SMART HULK, RHODEY, and NEBULA attach the Pym housing.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, Clint, you might feel a little disoriented when you chronoshift-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hang on, I’ve got to ask, if we can do this, why don’t we just go find baby Thanos and, you know...  Rhodey makes a STRANGLING GESTURE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Uh, one, because that’s horrible. And, two, killing baby Thanos doesn’t kill adult Thanos.  Time doesn’t work like that.  You can’t change the future by changing the past.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sure, we can.  We take the stones before Thanos gets them, then he doesn’t have them.  Problem solved.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s not how it works.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t know.  That is kind of what I’ve heard-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Heard from who?  49   50</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Star Trek.  Terminator.  Bill and Ted’s Excellent-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>WHY DOES EVERYONE THINK THIS? THAT’S NOT TRUE.  IF YOU TRAVEL TO THE PAST, THEN THAT PAST HAS BECOME YOUR PRESENT, AND YOUR FORMER PRESENT HAS BECOME THE PAST, WHICH NOW CAN’T BE CHANGED BY YOUR NEW FUTURE!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Exactly.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Excuse me?  Scott leans over, whispering:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Apparently, Back to the Future is bullshit.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Look, are we doing this or not?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, Clint.  Starting in three, two, one...  Clint nods over at them, determined.  SUDDENLY, HE STRETCHES, SHRINKS, AND VANISHES.  WHOOSH.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  Not yet... (opening the door) LILA!  BUT HIS BODY STARTS TO GLOW.  0.01-  CLINT VANISHES.  THE SCREEN DOOR SLAMS.  After a moment, LILA runs in.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>LILA BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Dad?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>LILA BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Are you all right?  Hey, look at me.  You okay?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tell me something good...  Clint looks up, tearful.  He holds out THE BASEBALL MITT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It worked.  It worked.  Reveal Steve, Smart Hulk, Nebula, Rhodey, Scott, Thor, and Rocket, looking on.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Holy crap.  We’re freaking time travelers.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay.  Now that we’ve got how, we’re going to need where and when.  NEBULA, TONY, RHODEY, SCOTT, SMART HULK, ROCKET, NATASHA, and CLINT look on.  STEVE (CONT'D) Most folks here have encountered at least one of the six Infinity Stones-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I think you mean nearly been killed by one of the six Infinity Stones.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I haven’t. (off their looks) Just...saying.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Regardless, we’ve only got enough Pym Particles for one round trip, each.  And the Stones have been in a lot of places throughout history.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Our history.  Not all of them are going to be a fun drop-in.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Which means we’ve got to pick our targets.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Exactly. (he taps “REALITY”) Let’s start with the Aether.  Thor, what do we know?  Everyone looks toward...THOR, slumped over.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Is he asleep?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m pretty sure he’s dead.  DISSOLVE TO:  THOR sulks, looking at the Aether Container Holo: “REALITY” Locations are listed: “SVARTALFHEIM, KNOWHERE, LONDON.”  52   (MORE)  53</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>The Aether’s not a stone, it’s more of an angry sludge.  My grandfather hid it from Dark Elves in a rock between dimensions that can only be accessed every 5000 years.  HIS ROBOTIC EYE drifts off in the wrong direction.  Thor bangs his head, resetting his eye.  THOR (CONT'D) Or...by Jane.  She stuck her hand in a rock.  Then the Aether stuck itself inside her.  Then I took her to Asgard.  We were dating... (depressed) We’re not anymore.  Everyone stares.  DISSOLVE TO:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Quill said he stole the Power Stone from Morag.  He paces on top of the table, past SMART HULK EATING A PINT OF “HUNKA HULKA BURNING FUDGE.”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s a person?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s a planet.  Quill was a person.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wait, like a planet...in space?  Rocket pinches Scott’s cheek.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Aw, look.  It’s like a puppy, all happy and everything. (MORE)  53   ROCKET (CONT'D)  54  You want to go to space, puppy? I’ll take you to space.  DISSOLVE TO:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thanos found the Soul Stone on Vormir.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And that is...?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>A dominion of death at the very center of celestial existence. (beat) It’s the place where Thanos murdered my sister.  That hangs heavily.  A moment passes.  Then...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not it.  DISSOLVE TO:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So this ‘Time Stone’ guy...what kind of doctor was he?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Strange?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Cross between ear-nose-and-throat and rabbit-from-hat.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Had a nice place in the Village.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  Sullivan Street.  ROCKET (CONT'D)  54   55</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Bleecker.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sullivan and Bleecker.  They’re cross streets.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wait, he lived in New York?  Guys, pick the right year and there were three stones in New York.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(beat) Shut the front door...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, we have a plan.  Six stones, three teams, one shot.  He steps away, revealing the board...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EVERYONE EYES THE TANGLE OF LINES CONNECTING SIX STONES TO</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>FOUR LOCATIONS TO TWO YEARS TO TEN HEROES.  IT’S INSANE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EVERYONE EYES THE TANGLE OF LINES CONNECTING SIX STONES TO</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We lost friends.  We lost family. We lost a part of ourselves. (beat) But today we have a chance to take it all back.  Steve takes in the groupings of heroes: RHODEY & NEBULA, NAT & CLINT, THOR & ROCKET, TONY & SCOTT.  55   56  STEVE (CONT'D) You have your teams and you have assignments.  Get your stone, and get back here.  One round trip each.  No mistakes.  No do-overs.  He grips HIS SHIELD.  STEVE (CONT'D) Most of us are going back to places we know.  That doesn’t mean we know what to expect.  Be careful.  Look out for each other.  Improvise, if you have to. (looking around) This is the fight of our lives. And we’re going to win. (beat) Whatever it takes.  The platform stays quiet.  Rocket WHISPERS to Scott:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He’s pretty good at that...  Scott nods enthusiastically.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(to Smart Hulk) All right, you heard the man. Stroke those keys, Jolly Green.  Smart Hulk taps in commands with HIS PENCIL.  LIGHTS ILLUMINATE EACH PAD.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tracking beacons engaged.  Clint checks his pocket: A SHRUNKEN BENATAR sits inside.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You promise to bring that thing back in one piece?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, sure thing.  I’ll do my best.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s pretty lame, as far as promises go.  SMART HULK STEPS ONTO THE PLATFORM, COMPLETING THE LINEUP. THE PLATFORM BEGINS TO VIBRATE.  NATASHA LOOKS AROUND.  56   57</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>See you in a minute.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Actually, it’ll be closer to seven or eight microseconds, give or-  SUDDENLY, THEY STRETCH AND VANISH, SHRINKING AWAY.  WHOOSH.  THE QUANTUM CONSOLE STOPS VIBRATING.  HULK’S PENCIL SLOWLY ROLLS TOWARD THE EDGE...AND DROPS OFF-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, Park Avenue’s that way. Let’s huddle up.  Suits off.  They all touch their cuffs, RETRACTING THEIR TIME SUITS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’ve all got our assignments.  Two stones uptown, one stone down. Stay low, keep an eye on time-  Just then, A1 HULK BOUNDS DOWN THE STREET SMASHING THINGS.  STEVE (CONT'D) And Bruce?  Maybe smash a few things along the way.  For appearances.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(taking off his shirt) All right, but I have to say, it seems gratuitous.  He half-heartedly smashes a few cars.  57   58  SMART HULK (CONT'D) Grrr...grrr...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hulk...does what...Hulk want?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yes, I suppose that would be the case-  JUST THEN, ON THE ROOF OPPOSITE, A1 HULK TACKLES A CHITAURI CHARIOT, RIPPING IT IN HALF.  HE ROARS, LEAPING AWAY.  Smart Hulk blinks, sheepish.  The Ancient One looks at him.  ANCIENT ONE (CONT'D) Care to explain?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m looking for Dr. Strange.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re about five years too early. Stephen Strange is currently performing surgery, 20 blocks that way.  What do you want with him?  He finally notices THE EYE OF AGAMOTTO HANGING FROM HER NECK.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Well, that, actually.  58   59</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Ah.  I’m afraid not.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m seriously sorry but...I wasn’t asking.  Smart Hulk cracks his knuckles and moves in.  She smiles.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You don’t want to do this.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re right, I don’t.  But I need that stone, and I don’t have a lot of time to debate it-  He reaches for it.  THE ANCIENT ONE SLAMS HER PALM INTO HIS CHEST AND BLASTS BRUCE BANNER RIGHT OUT OF SMART HULK.  “ASTRAL BANNER” hangs in the air, staring at his frozen Smart Hulk body.  He looks at his human hands, overwhelmed.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, no, no-  She topples Smart Hulk’s body with one finger.  Whump.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Now.  Let’s start over, shall we?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s Jane.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, here’s the deal.  You’re going to charm her, and I’m going to poke her with this thing, extract the Reality Stone, and get gone lickety-split.  Thor looks off in the other direction, anxious.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Um, I’ll be right back.  The wine cellar is just down here.  My father used to have this barrel of Aakonian ale.  Felt like getting hit in the face with a poleaxe. I’ll see if the scullery has a couple of to-go cups-  They hear SOMEONE APPROACHING.  Rocket yanks Thor back as...FRIGGA AND HER HANDMAIDENS ENTER THE CORRIDOR.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Send Loki some soup.  I don’t think he’s eating.  And ask our librarians to pull some volumes from the astronomy shelves.  He won’t read them, but at least they’ll keep him company.  Thor watches Frigga and her coterie disappear down the hall.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Who’s the fancy broad?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>My mother.  She dies today.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, jeez.  Thor starts to sweat.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I can’t do this.  This is a bad idea.  I can’t do this...  Rocket climbs onto a marble monument.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Come here.  60   (MORE)  61  Thor steps closer.  ROCKET SLAPS HIM ACROSS THE FACE.  ROCKET (CONT'D) You think you’re the only one who’s lost people?  What do you think we’re doing here?  I lost the only family I ever had.  Quill, Groot, Drax, the chick with the antenna. All gone.  I’ve lived five meaningless years without them, and every minute has blown Aaskvarian gornads.  I get you miss your mom. But she’s gone.  Really gone. There are plenty of people who are only kind of gone.  And you can help them.  So, is it too much to ask that you brush the crumbs out of your beard, make shmoopy talk to Prettypants, and when she’s not looking, suck out the Infinity Stone, and help me get my family back?  Thor stares at him a long moment.  He wipes his tears away.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I guess not.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you.  I can do this.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Great.  As Rocket scurries to Jane’s door, Thor murmurs to himself.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I can do this...I can do this... (beat) I can’t do this...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(peering through keyhole) All right, heartbreaker.  This is our shot...  Rocket turns to find...THOR NOWHERE TO BE SEEN.  ROCKET (CONT'D) Thor? (holding his temples) (MORE)  61   ROCKET (CONT'D)  62  I can kill him, and say the Elves did it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s it, right on that line, Blue.  Keep dropping it.  Nearby, CLINT SURVEYS THE PLANET.  GEYSERS EXPLODE.  CLIFFS LOOM.  AN ORLONI bites NATASHA’s boot.  She kicks it away.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(to Rhodey) Hey, can we hurry it up?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, come on, chop chop, we’re on the clock, here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>All that?  Really helpful!  TIME CUT:  Clint and Natasha board the Benatar.  Rhodey and Nebula remain on the planet’s surface.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Take care of yourself.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Get that stone and come back.  No messing around.  You guys watch each other’s six.  TIME CUT:  BESIDE THE POD, RHODEY AND NEBULA WATCH THE BENATAR TAKE OFF.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Coordinates for Vormir are laid in. All they have to do is not fall out.  ROCKET (CONT'D)  62   63</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Nothing.  Just...we’re a long way from Budapest.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(pushing the throttle) Further every second.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, all we have to do is hang out, wait for this Quill guy, and follow him to the Power Stone, right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Let’s take cover.  We’re not the only ones in this reality looking for the stones.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, who are you talking about right now?  Who else is looking for the stones?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>My father.  My sister.  And me.  MOVE IN ON RHODEY, CONCERNED.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You?  Where are you?  CUT TO:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re welcome?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I didn’t ask for your help.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And yet you always need it.  Father wants us back on the ship.  Gamora offers her hand.  Bad Nebula stands on her own.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Why?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He’s found an Infinity Stone.  Off Bad Nebula’s intrigued look...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>On a planet called “Morag.”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Ronan has located the Power Stone. I’m dispatching you to his ship.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He won’t like it.  Thanos wipes the blood from his blade.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>His alternative is death.  Ronan’s obsession clouds his judgement. After Loki, I’m taking no chances.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We will not fail you, father.  Thanos finally lays his eyes on her.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  You won’t.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I swear I will make you proud-  SUDDENLY, BAD NEBULA STAGGERS, hand to the wall.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sister, what’s-  65   66  Thanos watches, curious, as NEBULA DROPS TO A KNEE. SUDDENLY, A HOLO-PROJECTION OF RHODEY BEAMS FROM HER EYE.  RHODEY (HOLO) So, all we have to do is hang out, wait for this Quill guy, and follow him to the Power Stone, right?  NEBULA (HOLO) (O.S) Let’s take cover.  We’re not the only ones in this reality looking for the stones.  BAD NEBULA SLUMPS, breaking the projection.  Gamora goes to her, trying to prop her up.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Who was that?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I...don’t know.  My head...splitting...  Bad Nebula winces.  Gamora looks to Thanos.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Her synaptic drive was probably damaged in battle-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sshhh...  Thanos looks down at Bad Nebula.  He gently lifts her head with his blade.  Something’s not right.  THANOS (CONT'D) Bring her to my ship.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>LOKI</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>If it’s all the same to you...I’ll have that drink now.  From behind cover, TONY PEERS AT THE BACK SIDE OF THE AVENGERS TABLEAU.  TONY (INTO COM) Cap, I’ve got to say that outfit does nothing for your ass.  STEVE (OVER COM) No one asked you to look, Tony.  REVEAL TINY SCOTT ON TONY’S SHOULDER.  SCOTT LANG (INTO COM) I think you look great, Cap.  As far as I’m concerned, that’s America’s ass.  A1 NATASHA Who gets the magic wand?  A1 STEVE SHIELD’s coming up now.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>LOKI</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Ball’s in play.  Head’s up, Cap.  From hiding, Tony eyes A1 NATASHA WITH LOKI’S SCEPTER.  INTERCUT:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BROCK RUMLOW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We promise to be extra careful.  Scott stares at Sitwell and Rumlow.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BROCK RUMLOW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Who are these guys?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>SHIELD.  Actually, Hydra.  But we didn’t know that yet.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Seriously?  ‘Cause it’s kind of obvious they’re bad guys.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re small but you’re talking loud.  A1 THOR WALKS LOKI PAST A1 STEVE.  A1 STEVE (INTO COM) I’m on my way down to coordinate search and rescue.  Loki rolls his eyes...AND TRANSFORMS INTO A COPY OF STEVE.  LOKI/STEVE “I’m on my way down to coordinate search and rescue.”  I mean, really, how do you keep your food down?  Thor slaps A MUZZLE on Loki, who REVERTS TO HIS OWN FORM.  A1 THOR Yes, that’s much better.  He steers his brother into THE MAIN ELEVATOR.  A1 THOR (CONT'D) You coming, Stark?  68   69  Nearby, A1 TONY uses his gauntleted hand to place THE TESSERACT into AN ALUMINUM ATTACHE CASE.  A1 TONY One sec, just packing my lunch.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>All right, you’re up, Little Buddy. There’s our stone  A1 Tony crosses to the elevator.  Scott takes position, readying himself.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>All right.  Flick me.  Tony flicks Scott with a finger, sending him sailing into the ATTACHE CASE.  TONY leaps out the window, Bleeding Edge armor forming around him as he falls.  A1 Tony joins the others in the elevator.  Then...  A1 HULK steps up to THE ALREADY CROWDED ELEVATOR.  Avengers smile awkwardly.  There’s no room.  A1 HULK (angrily) Hulk take stairs.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Change of plans.  Steve glances at Rumlow, who’s holding THE SCEPTER.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BROCK RUMLOW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Cap.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BROCK RUMLOW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Rumlow.  The doors close.  Everyone rides in silence.  Tension mounts.  STEVE (CONT'D) I got a call from the Secretary’s office.  I’m going to be running point on the scepter.  Behind him, Sitwell and Rumlow exchange a glance.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>AGENT SITWELL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sir?  I don’t understand-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>AGENT SITWELL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’ve had word there might be an attempt to steal it.  Steve reaches for the scepter, but Rumlow holds tight.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BROCK RUMLOW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Afraid we can’t allow that, Cap.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>AGENT SITWELL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BROCK RUMLOW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(pulling out his phone) I’ll have to check with the Director-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>AGENT SITWELL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  Trust me.  It’s okay...  Steve leans in, drawing them all close.  Then he whispers:  70   71  STEVE (CONT'D) Hail Hydra.  THEIR EYES GO WIDE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Mind if I ask where you’re going?  A1 THOR We were thinking lunch, then Asgard.  And you are?  A1 TONY Alexander Pierce.  He’s the guy behind the guys behind Fury, so don’t mess.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>My friends call me Mr. Secretary. (to Thor) I have to ask you to turn the prisoner over to me.  A1 THOR Loki will answer to Odin, himself.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, he’ll answer to us.  “Odin” can have what’s left. (to Tony) And we’ll need the case back, too. That’s been SHIELD property for over seventy years.  A1 TONY I’m not gonna argue who has authority here but jurisdictionally speaking, we are on Stark property. That is my name on the glass...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Just give me the case.  Across the lobby, TONY OBSERVES FROM BEHIND HIS SWAT HELMET.  72   73  TONY (INTO COM) Move it, Stuart Little.  Things are getting dicey out here.  INTERCUT:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That doesn’t actually sound minor-  Tony sees PIERCE reaching for A1 TONY’S CASE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Window’s closing.  Pull my plug.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Here goes...  SCOTT YANKS THE WIRE OUT OF ITS SOCKET.  IN THE LOBBY, A1 TONY GRIPS HIS CHEST.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Stark?  A1 Tony SEIZES, dropping.  THE TESSERACT CASE CLATTERS TO THE GROUND.  PIERCE and A1 THOR kneel to assist.  ALEXANDER PIERCE (CONT'D) MEDIC!  A1 THOR Stark?  Somebody get some help!  Is it your chest machine?  THE LOBBY BUZZES, SHIELD AGENTS RUNNING EVERYWHERE.  In the bustle, SCOTT SLIDES OUT OF A1 TONY’S SLEEVE.  He SHOVES THE TESSERACT CASE HARD.  It SPINS across the floor...  RIGHT INTO TONY’S HAND.  Tony walks toward a side door.  73   74  TONY (INTO COM) Meet me in the alley.  I’m just gonna grab a slice at Famous Ray’s-  BUT AS TONY PASSES THE STAIRWELL DOOR...HULK BANGS IT OPEN, SMASHING TONY IN THE FACE, SENDING HIM TUMBLING.  A1 HULK BASHES HIS WAY THROUGH THE LOBBY.  The Tesseract Case hits the floor, popping open.  THE TESSERACT FALLS OUT, spinning past Tiny Scott...  STOPPING AT LOKI’S FEET.  Loki stares at it in disbelief.  He glances at A1 Thor and Pierce giving A1 Tony first aid.  THEN LOKI CALMLY REACHES DOWN WITH HIS MANACLED HANDS, GRASPS THE TESSERACT...AND TELEPORTS AWAY.  Scott stares, stunned.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ALEXANDER PIERCE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That wasn’t supposed to happen, was it?  A1 THOR LOOKS UP, REALIZING...  A1 THOR WHERE’S LOKI?  SHIELD TEAMS FAN OUT, ON ALERT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, great.  A1 STEVE (INTO COM) Disregard.  I have eyes on Loki, Fourteenth Floor.  74   75  STEVE GENTLY LAYS THE SCEPTER DOWN, AND PULLS OFF HIS SHIELD.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m not Loki.  And I don’t want to hurt you.  A1 STEVE PULLS HIS SHIELD OFF HIS BACK.  A1 STEVE You’re not going to get the chance-  A1 STEVE KICKS STEVE IN THE FACE.  Steve stumbles.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Forgot about that one.  They grapple.  Both their shields fall to the ground...  THEY BOTH STAMP ON THEM, simultaneously flipping the shields back to their arms.  A1 Steve looks impressed.  A1 STEVE SWINGS.  STEVE DUCKS, HAMMERING HIM.  A1 Steve wipes the blood from his lip, squaring off.  A1 STEVE I can do this all day-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, I know...  They battle on.  A1 Steve tackles Steve, knocking his shield aside, RIPPING OPEN ONE OF STEVE’S BELT COMPARTMENTS:  THE COMPASS FALLS OUT, OPENING TO REVEAL PEGGY’S PICTURE.  A1 Steve goes cold.  He picks up the compass, FLABBERGASTED.  A1 STEVE Where’d you get this?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>PX.  Camp Lehigh.  1943.  A1 Steve stares at Steve, eyes narrowing.  A1 STEVE You’ve got a lot of nerve.  HE HAMMERS STEVE ACROSS THE HALL.  Steve goes skidding.  He groans, looking up to see...HE’S INCHES FROM THE SCEPTER.  A1 STEVE moves in.  STEVE whips around, touching THE SCEPTER to A1 Steve’s chest.  A1 STEVE’S EYES GO BLACK.  HE FREEZES.  75   76  Steve stares, panting.  Finally, he picks up the compass from the floor, then considers A1 STEVE’S ASS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That is America’s ass.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, with all due respect, I’m not sure the science supports that.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And yet, you’re the one currently standing in the middle of my hydrangeas.  Banner looks down to see, indeed, he has phased through the middle of the hydrangeas.  He steps out of it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Lady, I just want to borrow your necklace-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>At what cost?  SHE CONJURES A MAGICAL PROJECTION OF THE INFINITY STONES, SPINNING IN UNISON.  A TUNNEL OF GOLDEN LIGHT POURS FORTH.  ANCIENT ONE (CONT'D) The Infinity Stones create the experience you know as the flow of time.  Remove one of the stones, and the flow splits.  She plucks the GREEN TIME STONE out of the array: A SMALLER, BLACKENED RIVER BRANCHES OFF FROM THE FIRST.  76   (MORE)  77  ANCIENT ONE (CONT'D) Now, your timeline might benefit. My new one...would definitely not.  SHE GESTURES.  OUR CAMERA ZOOMS INTO THE BLACKENED TUNNEL...  TUNNEL POV: HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE RUN AS WE FLY OVER A CROWDED STREET, UP TO...THE BURNING HONG KONG SANCTUM.  ANCIENT ONE (O.S.) (CONT'D) In this new branch reality, without our chief weapon against the forces of darkness, our world would be overrun...  MOVE UP TO SEE DORMAMMU IN THE SKY.  HE OPENS HIS MOUTH...  BACK ON THE ROOF...THE ANCIENT ONE PLUCKS MORE STONES FROM THE GOLDEN RIVER, CREATING FIVE MORE BLACKENED TRIBUTARIES.  ANCIENT ONE (CONT'D) For each stone you remove, you’ll create a new, vulnerable timeline. Millions will suffer. (beat) Now tell me, Doctor.  Can your science prevent all that?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  But it can erase it.  Astral Banner reaches in and grabs THE VIRTUAL TIME STONE.  ASTRAL BANNER (CONT'D) Because once we’re done with the stones, we can return each one to its own timeline.  At the moment it was taken.  So chronologically, in that reality, the stone never left.  HE PUTS THE TIME STONE BACK.  THE BLACK TIMELINE DISAPPEARS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re leaving out the most important part, though.  In order to put the stones back, you’d have to survive.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We will.  I will.  I promise.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I can’t risk this reality on a promise. (MORE)  77   ANCIENT ONE (CONT'D)  78  It is the duty of the Sorcerer Supreme to protect the Time Stone-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah?  Then why the hell did Strange give it away?  The Ancient One freezes.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What did you say?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Strange gave Thanos the Time Stone.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Willingly?  Why?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t know.  Maybe he made a mistake.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Or I did.  The Ancient One looks out over a recovering NYC.  ANCIENT ONE (CONT'D) Strange is meant to be the best of us.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ASTRAL BANNER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Then he must have had a reason.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ASTRAL BANNER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I fear you may be right...  Finally, she waves her hand and...WHOOSH!  HE REINTEGRATES INTO THE SMART HULK BODY.  Smart Hulk gets up, WOOZY.  SHE REMOVES THE TIME STONE FROM THE EYE, HANDING IT TO HIM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ANCIENT ONE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m counting on you, Bruce. (re. the city behind her) We all are.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ANCIENT ONE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Run diagnostics.  Show me her memory file.  At the console, EBONY MAW SCANS NEBULA’S INFORMATION. NEBULA’S BODY TWITCHES.  GAMORA WATCHES, TORN.  SOON...AN ALERT FLASHES.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EBONY MAW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sir, the file appears...entangled. It was a memory, but not hers. (dawning on him) There’s another consciousness sharing her network.  Another Nebula.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EBONY MAW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Impossible.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EBONY MAW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>This duplicate carries a time stamp...from nine years in the future.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EBONY MAW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where is this “other Nebula?”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EBONY MAW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>In our solar system.  On Morag.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EBONY MAW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Can you access her?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EBONY MAW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yes.  The two are linked.  THANOS PEERS INTO BAD NEBULA’S GLASSY EYES...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EBONY MAW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Search the duplicate’s memory for Infinity Stones.  Maw works the console.  Thanos steps aside as BAD NEBULA’S BODY QUIVERS.  AFTER A BEAT, A BEAM SHOOTS OUT OF HER EYE...  PROJECTING AN IMAGE OF AVENGERS COMPOUND:  79   80  STEVE, TONY, RHODEY, SCOTT, SMART HULK, ROCKET, NATASHA, CLINT, AND THOR GATHER IN THE LIVING AREA.  SMART HULK (HOLO) -the Stones have been in a lot of places throughout history.  TONY (HOLO) Our history.  Not all of them are going to be a fun drop-in.  CLINT BARTON (HOLO) Which means we’ve got to pick our targets.  STEVE (HOLO) Exactly.  Let’s start here-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Freeze image.  THE IMAGE FREEZES.  THANOS STARES, RECOGNIZING THEM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Terrans?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Avengers.  Unruly wretches.  He gestures to A BLURRY REFLECTION WITHIN THE HOLOGRAM.  THANOS (CONT'D) What’s this reflection.  Amplify this, Maw.  EBONY MAW ZOOMS IN, REVEALING...A REFLECTION OF NEBULA.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t understand.  Two Nebulas?  Thanos walks into the hologram, studying the faces.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  The same Nebula.  From two different times. (to Ebony Maw) Set course for Morag.  And scan the duplicate’s memories. (beat) I want to see everything...  80   81</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What are you doing?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Mother!  What?  Nothing.  Hello.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re better off leaving the sneaking to your brother. (re. his bathrobe) What are you wearing?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I always wear this.  It’s one of my favorites.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And what’s wrong with your eye?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, that.  You remember the...Battle of Harokin.  I took a...broadsword to the face?  He trails off, at a loss, staring at his dead mom.  Frigga gently lays her hand on his cheek...READING HIM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh.  You’re not the Thor I know at all, are you?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yes, I am-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I was raised by witches, boy.  I see with more than eyes, you know that. (eyeing him) I can see the future hasn’t been kind to you, has it?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I didn’t say I was from the future...  81   82</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thor...  Frigga gives her son a stern, “don’t lie to me” look.  Thor stares at his mom a long moment.  Then, he cracks:</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m totally from the future.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yes, you are.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I need to talk to you.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We can talk.  Frigga GRABS Thor by the cloak and yanks him away.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>...and then it was done.  His head over there.  Body over there.  And me in the middle.  Just an idiot with an axe.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re no idiot.  You’re here, aren’t you?  Seeking counsel from the smartest person in Asgard?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, I guess.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>An idiot, no.  A failure, absolutely.  82   83</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s a little harsh-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Quite a colossal one, by the sound of it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, maybe just stop talking.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And you know what that makes you? Just like everyone else.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m not supposed to be like everyone else, though.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Everyone fails at “who they’re supposed to be,” Thor.  The measure of a person, of a hero, is how well they succeed at being who they are.  Thor stares at her, biting back emotions.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’ve really missed you, Mum.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I got it I got it I got it!  A TROOP OF EINHERJAR CHASE AFTER HIM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Mum, I have to tell you something-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, son.  You don’t.  You’ve come to repair your future, not mine.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But your future-  83   84</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Is none of my business.  Thor stares at her, torn.  THEN ROCKET RACES INTO THE ROOM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(to Frigga) Hi.  You must be Mom. (to Thor, re. the device) I got the thing.  Come on, we gotta move-  Thor looks to Frigga.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I wish we had more time-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>This was a gift.  Now, go be the man you’re meant to be. (beat) And eat a salad.  Thor smiles.  He and Rocket activate their time suits.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Three...two-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  Wait.  THOR DRAMATICALLY HOLDS OUT HIS HAND.  A long moment passes.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What am I looking at?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sometimes it takes a second.  Then...MJOLNIR SAILS INTO HER SON’S HAND.  She grins, proud.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(relieved) Still worthy.  Mother and son look at each other for the last time.  THOR (CONT'D) Goodbye, Mum.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FRIGGA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Goodbye, Son.  THEN, WHOOSH!  THOR AND ROCKET DISAPPEAR.  84   85  Suddenly...THE PALACE RUMBLES.  Frigga looks to the window, WHERE A DARK ELF WARSHIP DECLOAKS.  SHE REACHES FOR A SWORD.  PRELAP: “COME AND GET YOUR LOVE,” BY REDBONE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FRIGGA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, he’s an idiot.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yes.  Quill spins, arms out, eyes shut.  When the horizon finally settles...he sees A METAL MAN STANDING THERE WAITING FOR HIM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, fu-  BAM!  RHODEY DECKS QUILL IN THE FACE.  Quill drops, out cold.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sorry about that.  I know you guys were teammates and everything.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Do you hear me complaining?  Nebula rifles through Quill’s sack.  She pulls out AN ELECTRONIC LOCK PICK.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What is that?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>The tool of a thief.  Come on.  They set out toward the RUINED CITY.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hang on.  This would be about the time the spikes come out, you know, with the skeletons still on them?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What are you talking about?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m just saying, when you break into a place called, “The Temple of the Power Stone”, there are usually...  Ahead, they see...THE POWER STONE ORB HOVERING ABOVE ITS PEDESTAL, SURROUNDED BY A WEB OF LASER THREADS.  RHODEY (CONT'D) Traps and stuff. (Nebula steps inside) Okay, don’t say I didn’t warn you.  Rhodey scans the laser web, strategizing.  RHODEY (CONT'D) These are photovoltaic lasers on a constantly shifting matrix.  Gonna be damn near impossible to neutralize unless we-  SUDDENLY, NEBULA REACHES HER CYBERNETIC ARM THROUGH THE WEB. SHE GRABS THE ORB...BUT THE WEB GRIPS HER, FRYING HER ARM.  She pulls out the orb, but sees Rhodey staring at HER BLACKENED CLAW.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I wasn’t always like this.  He sees actual emotion somewhere inside her.  Favor his exoskeletal leg braces as he softens.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah, me either.  I guess we do the best with what we’ve got, huh?  SHE HANDS HIM THE ORB WITH JUST THE GHOST OF A SMILE.  RHODEY (CONT'D) Let’s get out of here.  Place gives me the creeps.  Sync up.  Three... two...one...  86   (MORE)  87  RHODEY TAPS HIS CUFF, SHRINKING AWAY.  Nebula goes for hers...BUT HER EYES ROLL BACK.  SHE COLLAPSES, SEIZING VIOLENTLY, THEN GOING STILL.  Her eyes snap open, projecting a hologram of...THANOS.  THANOS (HOLO) What’s wrong?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What did you do to them?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Nothing.  Yet. (piecing it together) (MORE)  87   THANOS (CONT'D)  88  They’re not trying to stop something I’m going to do in our time.  They’re trying to undo something I’ve already done in theirs.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(uneasy) The stones.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I found them all.  I won.  Tipped the cosmic scales to balance.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EBONY MAW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sire.  This is your future?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EBONY MAW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>My destiny.  He stares, mind whirling.  He nods.  THE MEMORY RESUMES.  RHODEY (HOLO) He’s lying.  NEBULA (O.S.) My father is many things.  A liar is not one of them.  THANOS (HOLO) Thank you, daughter.  Perhaps I’ve treated you too-  WHUMP.  THOR CUTS OFF THANOS’ HEAD.  THE VIEW LINGERS AS “NEBULA” STARES AT HER DEAD FATHER.  THANOS STUDIES HIS SEVERED HEAD...AND SMILES.  THANOS (CONT'D) And that is destiny fulfilled.  Gamora stares, torn.  But Ebony Maw fumes on Thanos’ behalf.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EBONY MAW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sire.  Your daughter is a traitor.  EBONY MAW GESTURES: CABLES WRAP AROUND NEBULA’S NECK.  SHE AWAKENS, PANICKED.  She looks up at Thanos.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EBONY MAW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(choking) No.  Please, father.  That’s not me.  I would never betray you. Please-  THANOS (CONT'D)  88   89  Thanos UNWRAPS the cord.  He touches his daughter’s face.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Ssh, child.  I know.  And you’ll have the chance to prove it...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He knows...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’ve got a problem.  TIME CUT:  STEVE huddles with TONY and SCOTT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How could you lose it?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What do you want?  I got hit in the head with a Hulk!  89   90</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You said we only had one shot. This was our shot.  We shot it.  It was six stones or nothing!  Six stones-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re not helping-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You ruined the Time Heist!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, okay, Loki’s from Asgard, he’s comfortable there.  Knows the restaurants.  It’s a safe bet he visits home.  If we can just grab This-Thor and explain the situation, he and I can fly-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Loki could be anywhere in the universe.  We’d be old men before we found him.  As Steve and Scott debate, MOVE IN ON TONY, MIND WHIRLING...  STEVE (CONT'D) What other options did we have on the Tesseract?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Whoa, whoa.  We don’t have any other options.  We can’t go to any other times.  No do-overs!  We’ve only got one particle left, each. Use it now, that’s it, bye-bye, we don’t come home.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But if we don’t try, nobody else comes home, either.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I got it!  There’s another way to re-take the Tesseract, and acquire new particles. (to Steve) Military installation, Garden State.  Steve eyes Tony, BEGINNING TO UNDERSTAND.  90   91</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>When were they both there?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I have a vaguely exact idea.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How vague?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hang on, what’s in New Jersey?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I know they were there, and I know how I know.  STEVE STUDIES TONY A LONG MOMENT...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Looks like we’re improvising.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wait!  What are you improvising?  STEVE HANDS SCOTT THE STAFF.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Scott, take this back to the Compound.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>All right, suits on.  Try these coordinates. 04-07-19-70...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Steve- Cap- Captain America, if you do this and he’s wrong...you’re not coming back.  Steve and Tony let the weight of that sink in.  He’s right. Even so, Tony turns to Steve.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You trust me?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I do.  THEY STARE AT EACH OTHER, THEN...CLICK.  THEY BOTH HIT THEIR CUFFS.  TONY AND STEVE SHRINK TO NOTHING...  91   92</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STAN LEE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Make love, not war, baby!  He roars off, passing A FADED SIGN: “U.S. ARMY - CAMP LEHIGH - BIRTHPLACE OF CAPTAIN AMERICA.”  MOVE INTO THE BASE...  TONY (O.S.) You weren’t actually born here, right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STAN LEE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>The idea of me was.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(looking around) All right.  If I was SHIELD and I wanted to hide my quasi-fascistic black site, where would I hide it?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>In plain sight.  Steve nods at A MAN IN A GRAY SUIT approaching a building, “MUNITIONS.”  He opens the door with a retro-tech PUNCH CARD.  TONY TOUCHES HIS GLASSES: HE X-RAYS INTO THE GROUND, ILLUMINATING...TWENTY FLOORS OF SECRET, UNDERGROUND BASE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good luck with that mission, Captain.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good luck with your project, Doctor.  Tony ducks out.  The doors close.  The Agent turns to Steve.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You new here?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not exactly.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Come on, you little hexahedron, where are you hiding?  Finally, he spots A HIGH TECH SAFE.  He grabs a briefcase, then NANOS A GAUNTLET, FRYING THE SAFE’S LOCK.  It opens revealing...THE TESSERACT.  Tony smiles.  TONY (CONT'D) You may not know it now, but someday you’re going to be a real pain-in-the-ass.  Just then...THE ARCHIVE DOOR OPENS.  HOWARD STARK (O.S.) Hey, Arnim, you in here?  TONY LOCKS THE CUBE IN THE BRIEFCASE JUST BEFORE...  HOWARD STARK (49) APPEARS, carrying ROSES AND A CAN OF SAUERKRAUT.  TONY STARES, STUNNED.  HOWARD STARK (CONT'D) Hey, I’m looking for Dr. Zola.  You seen him?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  Haven’t seen a soul.  93   94  Tony stands in front of his father, overwhelmed.  Howard looks at him, a bit suspicious.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I know you?  From his pocket, TONY GENERATES A BADGE OUT OF NANO-TECH.  He holds it out.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, sir.  Just visiting from MIT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That so?  Got a name?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Howard...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Easy to remember-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Potts.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m Howard Stark. (shaking hands) You seem a little green around the gills, Potts.  Need some air?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’d be swell.  Tony distractedly walks away, leaving the briefcase.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Need the briefcase?  PRE-LAP A RINGING PHONE...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HANK PYM</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Maybe I’m confused.  Isn’t that your job?  STEVE (OVER PHONE) It’s just...sir, the box is glowing.  And to be honest, a couple of our mail guys aren’t feeling great-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HANK PYM</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HANK PYM</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>They didn’t open it, did they?!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HANK PYM</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sauerkraut and a bouquet...big night planned?  95   96</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(lifting one at a time) My wife’s expecting.  And too much time at the office.  Tony puzzles the dates out in his head...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Congratulations.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thanks.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How far along is she?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Gee, I suppose... (indicating) ...this far.  She’s at the point where she can’t stand the sound of my chewing.  So I guess I’ll be eating in the pantry again.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I have a little girl.  TONY SMILES.  He’s talking about the man-he’s-talking-to’s granddaughter, fifty years before she’s born.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>A girl would be nice.  Less chance she’d turn out exactly like me.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Would that be so bad?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Let’s just say the greater good hasn’t always outweighed my own self interest.  The elevator doors open.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  But I have an eye for this. Something looked fishy.  M.P. Describe ‘fishy’.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>One of them had a hippie beard.  M.P. We talking Bee Gees or Mungo Jerry?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Definitely Mungo Jerry.  M.P. (over walkie-talkie) This is Chesler.  We need every available agent to sub-level 6.  We have a potential breach.  Steve ducks through the nearest door...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEGGY CARTER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>FEMALE SHIELD AGENT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So, send them in.  97   98</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MALE AGENT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEGGY CARTER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>They’re trying, ma’am, but Braddock’s unit has been stopped by lightning strikes.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEGGY CARTER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MALE AGENT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, for the love of- I’ll find the weather projections.  You call Braddock and tell him to shelter in place.  Assuming he’s bright enough to come out of the rain.  MALE AGENT (O.S.) Yes, ma’am.  Steve stares at her from the darkness, STUNNED.  Peggy rifles through a file cabinet.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEGGY CARTER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEGGY CARTER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Here we are...  She flips through a file, reading.  In the darkness behind her, Steve approaches.  Peggy reads something disturbing.  PEGGY CARTER (CONT'D) Crikey O’Reilly. (calling out) Sergeant?  Hang up and call Air Command.  Braddock needs back up, immediately.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MALE AGENT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEGGY CARTER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Ma’am?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEGGY CARTER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MALE AGENT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Those aren’t lightning strikes he’s looking at...  She slaps the file closed and hurries out.  Steve stares after her a long moment.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEGGY CARTER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Got any names, yet?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>If it’s a boy, my wife likes Elmonzo.  98   99</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You might let that stew a while. You’ve got time.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What are you, couple years older than me?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  I guess.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Let me ask you a question.  When your kid was born...were you nervous?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wildly.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Did you feel qualified?  Like you had any idea how to successfully operate that thing?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I pieced it together as I went along.  I thought about what my dad did...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>My old man never met a problem he couldn’t solve with a belt.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I tried to hold onto the good stuff.  Dad dropped the odd pearl, here and there.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Like what?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>“No amount of money ever bought a second of time.”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s good.  Smart guy.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He did his best.  99   100</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I tell you, this kid’s not even here yet, but there’s nothing I wouldn’t do for him.  Tony takes this in, GRATIFIED.  Just then...EDWIN JARVIS (56) opens the limo door.  HOWARD STARK (CONT'D) Besides, if I fall down on the fathering job, old Jarvis is ready to pick up the slack.  Isn’t that right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EDWIN JARVIS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Indeed, sir.  I shall endeavor to teach the lad the rudiments of judo.  Tony smiles at his old friend.  As Jarvis gets in the car, Tony notices...STEVE WAITING BEHIND A JEEP.  TIME TO GO.  Howard turns to shake Tony’s hand.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EDWIN JARVIS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Well, good to meet you, Potts.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re going to do fine, Howard.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thanks.  See you around?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Count on it...  As he gets into his car, Howard looks to Jarvis.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Have we met him before?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EDWIN JARVIS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’ve met a lot of people, sir.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOWARD STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EDWIN JARVIS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Seems very familiar. (beat) Weird beard.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOWARD STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re weak.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m you-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Shut up!  BAD NEBULA PUNCHES GOOD NEBULA DOWN.  GOOD NEBULA GROANS AS BAD NEBULA RIPS OFF HER TIME-SPACE GPS.  THEN GAMORA ENTERS.  Nebula softens, taking in her (once dead) sister.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You could stop this.  You know you want to. (off Gamora’s look) Did you see what happens in the future?  Thanos finds the Soul Stone.  MOVE IN ON GAMORA, WHEELS TURNING...  NEBULA (CONT'D) You want to know how he does that? You want to know what he does to you-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>ENOUGH!  BAD NEBULA SMACKS HER THE HARDEST YET, THEN LEANS IN WITH A JAGGED INSTRUMENT OF TORTURE.  BAD NEBULA (CONT'D) You disgust me...but that doesn’t mean you’re useless.  SHE PRIES OFF THE ORANGE PANEL FROM GOOD NEBULA’S HEAD.  Gamora takes in this new development...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How do I look?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Under different circumstances, this would be totally awesome.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Really starting to regret my choice here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  I’m gonna bet the raccoon didn’t have to climb a mountain.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t think technically he’s a raccoon...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Whatever.  He eats garbage-  102   103  THEY HEAR SOMETHING.  THEY WHIRL, WEAPONS UP.  A HOODED FIGURE APPROACHES.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOODED FIGURE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I assure you, you have nothing to fear from me.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOODED FIGURE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Creepy.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOODED FIGURE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Welcome Natasha, daughter of Ivan. Clint, son of Edith.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOODED FIGURE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Creepier.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Who are you?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RED SKULL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Consider me a guide.  To you, and to all who seek the Soul Stone.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RED SKULL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Great.  You show us where it is, and we’ll be on our way.  The figure removes his hood, revealing...THE RED SKULL.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RED SKULL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, liebchen.  If only it were that easy...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RED SKULL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RED SKULL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What you seek lies in front of you. As does what you fear.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RED SKULL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>The Stone is down there?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RED SKULL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>For one of you.  For the other... (smiling it away) The Stone demands a sacrifice.  In order to take it, you must leave behind that which you love.  103   104  SKULL POINTS A BONY FINGER DOWN THE WELL.  RED SKULL (CONT'D) A soul for a soul.  Natasha and Clint stare down the well, stunned.  TIME CUT:  RED SKULL STARES DOWN THE WELL, robes whipping in the wind.  CLINT BARTON (O.S.) Maybe he’s full of shit.  FIFTY FEET AWAY, AT THE MONOLITHS, NATASHA AND CLINT HUDDLE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RED SKULL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t think so.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Why, because he knew your daddy’s name?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I didn’t. (off his look) Thanos left here with the stone, and without his daughter.  You really think that’s a coincidence?  They both look out at the well, heavy.  NATASHA (CONT'D) (under her breath) Whatever it takes...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(under his breath) Whatever it takes...  Natasha goes to Clint, resolved.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>If we don’t get the stone, billions of people are going to stay dead.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Then I guess we both know who it has to be.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  Guess we do.  They take each other’s hand.  A long goodbye beat.  Except...  104   105</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m starting to think we don’t mean the same person.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>For the last five years, I’ve been trying to do one thing -- get to right here.  This is all it’s been about.  Bringing everybody back.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Do not get all decent on me-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You think I want to do it?  I’m trying to save your life, you idiot-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And I don’t want you to. (beat) Nat.  You know what I’ve done. What I am now.  Your life’s worth ten of mine-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t judge people by their worst mistakes-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Maybe you should-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You didn’t.  That stops him.  He looks in her eyes, then down, giving in.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re a pain in my ass, you know that?  She relaxes for the briefest moment.  Just then, CLINT SWEEPS OUT HER LEGS, PINNING HER DOWN.  CLINT BARTON (CONT'D) Tell my family I love them.  SHE REVERSES, SENDING HIM TUMBLING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tell them yourself.  SHE FIRES A WIDOW’S BITE INTO HIS CHEST AND MAKES A BREAK FOR THE CLIFF.  SHE’S HALFWAY THERE WHEN...  105  ---   106  BOOM!  AN EXPLODING ARROW KNOCKS HER OFF HER FEET.  Clint races past her...leaping off edge of the cliff.  Just as he falls...  NATASHA TACKLES HIM IN MID-AIR.  They drop, but NATASHA SHOOTS HER GRAPPLING LINE INTO THE CLIFF.  THEY SLAM INTO THE CLIFFSIDE.  She attaches the other end of her grappling line to Clint’s belt...saving his life.  She slides, but he reaches out and grabs her...saving hers.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Damn you.  They hang there a long, terrible moment.  CLINT’S GRASP STARTS TO LOOSEN.  Finally, she looks him in the eye.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Let me go.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  Please no...  The two friends stare at each other, a lifetime between them.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NATASHA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s okay...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NATASHA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Natasha, no-  Then Natasha Romanoff kicks off the cliff wall, yanking out of Clint’s grasp.  She falls...  Clint dangles from the grappling hook, staring down, helpless, stifling his scream.  WHOOSH!  THE WHOLE WORLD GOES WHITE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Are you telling me that actually worked?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Did we get them all?  CLINT DROPS TO HIS KNEES.  Steve turns, concerned.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Clint?  Are you okay?  Clint stares, haunted.  SMART HULK realizes...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where’s Nat? (everyone stares) WHERE’S NAT?!  Clint looks up at them, eyes glassy.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Do we know if she had family?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  Us.  Thor turns, thrown.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Why are you doing that?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m just asking a question-  107   108</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Why are we talking as if she’s dead?  We have the stones.  Bring her back.  C’mon, stop this shit.  Clint squeezes away tears.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We can’t get her back.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What’s he talking about?  Of course, we can.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It can’t be undone.  That’s why.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No offense, but you’re...a very earthly being.  We’re talking about space magic, here.  “Can’t” seems a little definitive, don’t you think?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Well, I know I’m a little outside my pay grade here, but, she still isn’t here, is she?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s my point-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It can’t be undone.  At least that’s what the red, floating guy said.  But why don’t you go talk to him, okay?  Why don’t you grab your hammer and fly to that place and talk to him.  IT CAN’T BE UNDONE. (beat) It was supposed to be me.  She sacrificed her life for that goddamn stone.  She bet her life on it.  That lands heavily on all of them.  A moment passes.  THEN SMART HULK HURLS THE BENCH INTO THE WATER.  It skips across the surface like a stone.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>She’s not coming back.  We have to make it worth it.  We have to.  108   109</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We will.  PULL BACK, LEAVING OUR MOURNERS IN TABLEAU...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>All right.  The glove’s ready. Question is, who’s gonna snap their freaking fingers?  Everyone stares a beat.  Then, THOR REACHES FOR THE GAUNTLET.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’ll do it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Whoa, whoa, what are you doing-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thor, we haven’t decided who’s putting that on.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh.  Were all of you just waiting for the right opportunity?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Maybe I was getting around to it-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We should at least discuss it-  109   110</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Staring at the thing isn’t going to bring everybody back, is it?  Look, I’m the strongest Avenger.  It’s my responsibility.  Fate wills it so.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hold on, hold on-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Stop it!  Let me do this.  Let me do something good.  Something right-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That thing is channeling enough energy to light up a continent. You’re in no condition-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What do you think is coursing through my veins right now?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Cheez Whiz?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Lightning.  Smart Hulk steps toward the Gauntlet.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Lightning won’t help you, pal. It’s gotta be me. (approaching) You saw what those stones did to Thanos.  They almost killed him. None of you could survive.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And how do we know you can?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We don’t.  But the radiation’s mostly gamma. (beat) It’s like I was made for this...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Good to go?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Let’s do it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Okay, remember, everyone Thanos snapped away five years ago, you’re just bringing them back...to today. Don’t change anything from the last five years.  Got it?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Got it.  PAN AROUND as the Avengers ready themselves:  STEVE steps forward, shield on his arm.  SCOTT deploys his helmet.  RHODEY readies his repulsors.  ROCKET covers his raccoon junk and hides behind THOR.  TONY armors up, then nanos a shield to protect CLINT beside him.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Friday, why don’t you go ahead and activate Barn Door Protocol?  STEEL DOORS SLIDE SHUT ALL AROUND THE WORKSHOP.  FINALLY, SMART HULK HOLDS UP THE GAUNTLET.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(under his breath) Everybody’s coming home...  HE SLOWLY SLIPS HIS HAND IN THE GLOVE.  SUDDENLY, HE SPASMS, TAKING IN THE POWER AS THANOS DID IN ML1.  HE STRUGGLES.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What’s happening?  Take it off, take if off!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Bruce, you okay?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Talk to me, Banner.  111   112</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m...okay...  THEN SMART HULK REACHES OUT HIS HAND...AND SNAPS HIS FINGERS.  CRAAAACK!  THE STONES FLARE.  A BRIGHT SURGE OF ENERGY RACES UP SMART HULK’S ARM.  HE ROARS AS HIS EYES BLAZE GREEN.  A BLAST WHITES OUT THE SCREEN.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Bruce!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t move him!  Then THE BLAST DOORS OPEN, revealing the sound of...CHIRPING. SCOTT walks toward the courtyard.  Smart Hulk’s eyes clear.  He grasps Steve’s arm.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Did it work?  They pause, as if it only just now occurred to them.  JUST THEN...A CELL PHONE BUZZES.  112   113  A STUNNED CLINT TURNS AND APPROACHES HIS PHONE.  On the home screen, we see A PHOTO OF HIS WIFE: “LAURA CALLING.”  CLINT FINALLY PUTS THE PHONE TO HIS EAR.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Honey?  AT THE WINDOW, SCOTT STARES AT A BIRD FEEDER.  DOZENS OF CARDINALS AND FINCHES NIBBLE ON THE SEED.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Guys, I think it-  BOOM!  THE BUILDING EXPLODES.  DEBRIS SWALLOWS THE CAMERA.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So this is the future.  Well done.  She tears off THE ORANGE HEAD-PLATE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you, Father.  They suspected nothing.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>The arrogant never do.  113   114  Thanos takes off his helmet, staring up at the crater’s edge.  THANOS (CONT'D) Go.  Find the stones.  Bring them to me.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What will you do?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wait.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Canopy!  Canopy!  Rhodey’s suit RATCHETS OPEN.  HE HAULS HIMSELF FREE to see...ROCKET TRAPPED UNDER RUBBLE.  AS HE CRAWLS TO HIM...  THE CEILING RUMBLES.  SMART HULK WAVERS, MUSCLES QUIVERING.  RHODEY (INTO COM) (CONT'D) Mayday!  Tony.  Cap.  Does anybody hear me?!  HE FINALLY REACHES ROCKET.  Rocket wheezes, in pain.  RHODEY (CONT'D) Hang on!  RHODEY WEDGES A PIECE OF REBAR INTO THE DEBRIS.  HE HEAVES, finally managing to lever it off of Rocket.  THEN...  THE CRACKED CEILING GIVES WAY.  A MILLION GALLONS OF RIVER WATER RUSH IN.  RHODEY TRIES TO KEEP HIS HEAD ABOVE WATER.  RHODEY (INTO COM) (CONT'D) Mayday!  Mayday!  We are taking on water!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wait, what...?  REVEAL, TINY SCOTT LYING IN THE RUINS OF THE ARMORY...ON THE IRON PATRIOT HELMET.  ROCKET (OVER COM) Tell ‘em to...hurry...asses up-  RHODEY (OVER COM) ...trapped...drowning...no time...  Scott jumps to his feet.  SCOTT LANG (INTO COM) No!  Wait, I’m here!  Scott spots WATER TRICKLING THROUGH THE CRACKED FLOOR.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>WATER DRIPS FROM A HOLE IN THE ROOF OF AN ACCESS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>TUNNEL...ONTO CLINT BARTON, LYING FACEDOWN.  He groans.  He opens his hand to find HIS CELLPHONE: HIS WIFE SMILES ON THE SCREEN.  “LAURA, ONE MISSED CALL.”  Clint stares, amazed.  He winces, finding he’s been lying atop...THE GAUNTLET.  It’s bashed out of shape, BUT ALL SIX STONES STILL GLEAM.  CLINT BARTON (INTO COM) Cap?  Stark?  Anyone?  STATIC.  Then, he hears...A SCRAPING SOUND, TALONS ON CEMENT.  He peers down a darkened tunnel, then unshoulders his bow. HE LOOSES A FLARE ARROW, revealing...  DOZENS OF OUTRIDERS SCRABBLING ALONG THE WALLS AND CEILING. CLINT GRABS THE GAUNTLET AND RUNS.  THE CREATURES GIVE CHASE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>WATER DRIPS FROM A HOLE IN THE ROOF OF AN ACCESS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You lose this again, I’m keeping it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What happened?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Told you.  We messed with time. Time messed back.  Woozy, Steve follows Tony through the ruins of the lab.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where are the others?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I read life signs, maybe 800 feet down, but it’s hard to tell.  They reach the edge of the crater where THOR LOOKS DOWN AT...THANOS.  Sitting on a rock.  Waiting.  TONY (CONT'D) What’s he been doing?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Absolutely nothing.  The three of them stare a long moment.  Then, as if sensing them, Thanos turns his head...AND LOOKS THEIR WAY.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Son of a bitch.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where are the stones?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Somewhere under all of this.  All I know is...he doesn’t have ‘em.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So we keep it that way.  That lands.  This is their chance.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You know it’s a trap.  TONY DEPLOYS HIS ARMOR.  116   (MORE)  117</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Don’t think I care.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Just so we’re all in agreement.  Thor holds out his hand: MJOLNIR FLIES INTO IT.  He holds out his other hand: STORMBREAKER SLAPS INTO HIS PALM.  CRACK!  LIGHTNING STRIKES AS HE’S COVERED IN CAPE AND ARMOR.  THOR (CONT'D) Let’s kill him properly this time.  STEVE TIGHTENS HIS SHIELD, LEADING THEM INTO THE CRATER...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You could not live with your own failure.  And where did that bring you?  Right back to me.  TONY APPROACHES, WARY, AS IF SNEAKING UP ON A RABID DOG. STEVE AND THOR FAN OUT ON EITHER SIDE.  THANOS (CONT'D) I thought by eliminating half of life, the other half would thrive. But you’ve shown me that’s impossible. (beat) Life clings to the past with bloody fingernails.  As long as there are those who remember what was, there will be those unable to accept what can be.  They will resist.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yep.  We’re all kinds of stubborn.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m thankful.  Because now I know what I must do.  Thanos reaches for his helmet.  THANOS (CONT'D) I will shred this universe down to its last atom. (MORE)  117   THANOS (CONT'D)  118  And then, with the stones you’ve collected for me, create a new one, teeming with life that knows not what it has lost, but only what it has been given.  A grateful universe.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Born out of blood.  Thanos studies Steve as if seeing him for the first time.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>They’ll never know it.  THANOS DRAWS A BLADE OFF HIS BACK, TOWERING OVER THEM.  THANOS (CONT'D) Because you won’t be alive to tell them.  Tony glances over at Steve.  Ready?  Steve nods...  JUST AS THOR CHARGES THANOS.  WHAM!  ALL THREE AVENGERS ATTACK, USING THEIR SKILLS IN CONCERT.  THANOS STUMBLES, ON HIS HEELS.  THE HEROES PUNISH HIM, RELENTLESS.  PULL UP THROUGH THE HAZE, TO THE SANCTUARY-2...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What do you want?  GAMORA STEPS INTO THE CELL.  THE TWO SISTERS FROM DIFFERENT ERAS STARE AT EACH OTHER.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>In the future...what happens to you and me?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I try to kill you.  Several times. But, eventually...we become friends.  We become sisters.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s hard to believe.  THANOS (CONT'D)  118   119</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>A lot of things that happen will be hard to believe.  Gamora nearly smiles.  She takes a long look at Nebula. Finally...SHE HOLDS OUT HER HAND.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Come on.  We can still stop him.  Nebula takes a deciding moment.  Then SHE GRABS GAMORA’S HAND.  One sister pulls the other to her feet.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Rhodey.  Rocket.  Get out of here. Save yourselves.  ROCKET SURFACES FROM BELOW, GASPING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No good.  Couldn’t even...find a hole...small enough to abandon you through.  Suddenly, Smart Hulk snarls in pain as THE CEILING DROPS A FOOT.  His legs buckle as he struggles against the weight.  Finally he sets his jaw...AND STRAIGHTENS HIS LEGS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>AAARRRGH!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, hey.  I know you.  She gently takes the Gauntlet.  BAD NEBULA (INTO COM) Father.  I have the stones.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What-  Clint tries to get up, but Nebula puts a boot in his chest and A BLASTER TO HIS HEAD...  GAMORA (O.S.) Stop.  COVERING CLINT, BAD NEBULA TURNS TO SEE...GAMORA, GUN RAISED.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re betraying us?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Not you.  GOOD NEBULA steps from the shadows, hands raised, placating. Bad Nebula stares at her future self.  120   121</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You don’t have to do this.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I am this.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  You’re not.  Good Nebula takes a tiny step forward.  She taps her head.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’ve seen what we become-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sister, listen to her-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Shut up.  You’re a traitor!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You can change.  Bad Nebula struggles, her face a twisted grimace.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BAD NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>He won’t let me.  BAD NEBULA FIRES AT GAMORA, JUST AS GOOD NEBULA DRAWS A GUN AND SHOOTS HER DOWN.  BAD NEBULA DROPS.  Good Nebula stares at her dead younger self, conflicted.  Clint picks up the gauntlet, very confused.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BAD NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m not even gonna ask.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS SNATCHES TONY BY THE ANKLE  AND USES HIM AS A SHIELD</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>AGAINST THE ONCOMING HAMMER.  WHACK!  121   122  MJOLNIR PLOWS INTO THE DIRT.  TONY GOES TUMBLING, OUT COLD.  TONY’S HUD: FRIDAY TRIES TO REVIVE HIM.  FRIDAY (O.S.) Boss?  Wake up!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>RHODEY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS SNATCHES TONY BY THE ANKLE  AND USES HIM AS A SHIELD</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>See you on the other side, man.  They take a last breath, THEN THE WATER HITS THE CEILING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>RHODEY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I...knew...it...  STEVE ATTACKS, CRACKING THANOS IN THE JAW.  THANOS TUMBLES.  BEFORE THE TITAN CAN GET UP, STEVE CALLS DOWN THE LIGHTNING AND SENDS IT CRACKLING INTO THANOS’ BODY.  Steve leaps, trying to finish Thanos off...BUT THANOS ROLLS ASIDE, HEAD-BUTTING STEVE BACKWARDS.  THANOS GETS TO HIS FEET, A FAINT SMILE ON HIS FACE.  HE WHIPS OFF HIS HELMET AND ATTACKS STEVE WITH HIS BLADE. BLOW AFTER BLOW.  IT’S ALL STEVE CAN DO TO GET HIS SHIELD UP.  122   123  THANOS HACKS THE SHIELD TO PIECES, FINALLY KNOCKING STEVE ACROSS THE FIELD.  Steve lies beaten, half a shield still attached to his arm.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>In all my years of conquest...  Thanos looks out at the tiny human struggling to stand.  THANOS (CONT'D) Of violence and slaughter...it was never personal.  Thanos gestures behind him as A RUMBLE ECHOES.  THOUSANDS OF ALIENS RING THE LIP OF THE CRATER: THE BLACK ORDER LEADS A PLATOON OF CHITAURI, SAKAARANS, AND OUTRIDERS.  THANOS (CONT'D) But I’ll tell you now, the things I’m about to do to your stubborn, annoying, little planet...  Q-SHIPS, DROPSHIPS, NECROCRAFT, AND LEVIATHANS BUZZ ABOVE.  THANOS (CONT'D) I’m going to enjoy it.  Very, very much.  Steve stares at Thanos and his army.  And even in the face of such overwhelming odds...he gets to his feet.  THANOS stares, almost sad, as Steve tightens the broken shield on his arm...AND STARTS WALKING TOWARD HIM.  One man against thousands.  All alone.  But just then, Steve’s COM CRACKLES.  He strains to hear. The com crackles again.  We can make out A MUFFLED VOICE.  MUFFLED VOICE (ON COM) -ap-...-comin-...-ot-  Steve shakes his head, trying to clear it.  Slowly, SOUND RETURNS...AND THE WORDS RING CLEAR:  SAM WILSON (O.S.) Cap.  On your left.  PULL BACK...TO SEE A PORTAL OPENING IN THE DISTANCE.  OUT OF IT FLIES...SAM WILSON.  123   124  Steve watches Sam soar over the field, then turns AS EVEN MORE PORTALS OPEN.  FROM ONE: DR. STRANGE, PETER QUILL, DRAX, MANTIS, PETER PARKER...AND KRAGLIN AND THE RAVAGERS.  FROM ANOTHER: T’CHALLA, OKOYE, SHURI, M’BAKU, WANDA, BUCKY, GROOT...AND THE WAKANDAN ARMY.  FROM A THIRD: VALKYRIE, KORG, MIEK...AND AN ASGARDIAN ARMY.  FROM A FOURTH: PEPPER POTTS (IN RESCUE ARMOR), HOPE VAN DYNE, AND WONG LEADING A SQUAD OF SORCERERS.  THOR gets to his feet, calling Stormbreaker to his hand as...TONY regains consciousness, staring out at the cavalry.  Wong and Strange quickly find each other.  DR. STRANGE Is that everyone?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>WONG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You wanted more?!  JUST THEN, THE GROUND SHAKES AND RUBBLE EXPLODES UPWARDS AS...GIANT-MAN BURSTS FROM BELOW.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>WONG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Top floor, everybody out!  HE OPENS HIS HUGE HAND, RELEASING ROCKET, SMART HULK, AND RHODEY, NOW IN HIS COSMIC IRON PATRIOT ARMOR.  STEVE TAKES IN HIS REINFORCEMENTS, THEN STARES OUT AT THANOS.  PAN ACROSS OUR HEROES AS STEVE CALLS MJOLNIR TO HIS HAND.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Avengers...assemble.  THOR LETS LOOSE A BATTLE CRY AS HE CHARGES!  EVERYONE FOLLOWS SUIT AS OUR HEROES FLOOD THE FIELD.  ACROSS THE WAY, THANOS SMILES AND POINTS HIS BLADE.  TWO MIGHTY ARMIES RACE TOWARD EACH OTHER UNTIL...CLASH!  GIANT-MAN SLUGS A LEVIATHAN IN THE JAW.  DRAX launches himself onto a CULL currently choking the life out of KORG.  124   125  TONY blasts overhead.  RESCUE joins him.  Together, they strafe the field.  STEVE and THOR fight together.  Both hold out their hands. Stormbreaker returns to Steve, Mjolnir to Thor, who frowns.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No.  You take the little one.  Elsewhere, TONY BATTLES SEVERAL CULLS.  One knocks him into an Outrider, who’s about to rip his armor off when...  THWIP.  PETER PARKER webs the Outrider, yanking him into the path of...GIANT-MAN’S FOOT.  SQUISH.  Tony stares at Peter, emotional.  They retract their helmets.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PETER PARKER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Mr. Stark.  Holy cow, you would not believe what’s been going on.  Do you remember when we were in space? And I got all dusty?  I must’ve passed out, because I woke up and you weren’t there, but Dr. Strange was, and he was like, “it’s been five years, they need us.”  And he started doing that yellow sparkly thing he does-  But Tony just wraps his arms around him, smashing Peter’s face into his chest plate.  PETER PARKER (CONT'D) (muffled) Oh.  This is nice.  ACROSS THE FIELD...QUILL flies, firing down on Sakaaran soldiers.  One leaps off an outcropping...  TACKLING QUILL INTO A WRECKED FUSELAGE, WHERE ANOTHER SAKAARAN WAITS.  Quill drops one, but the other raises his weapon to strike. THEN BLAM!  The Sakaaran drops dead on top of Quill.  He pushes the body off to see...GAMORA, BLASTER STILL SMOKING.  Quill stares, amazed.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PETER PARKER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Gamora?  HE APPROACHES, OVERWHELMED, EMOTIONAL.  125   126  QUILL (CONT'D) I thought I lost you.  He tenderly strokes her face...and she knees him in the nuts. Twice.  He goes down, gasping.  QUILL (CONT'D) You missed the first time...then you got ‘em both the second time.  She stares down at him as...NEBULA JOINS HER.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GAMORA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>This is the one?  Seriously?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GAMORA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Your choices were him or a tree.  ACROSS THE FIELD...CLINT RUNS WITH THE GAUNTLET, PURSUED BY A CHITAURI APE.  Just before the ape tramples Clint...  SAM WILSON SWOOPS IN, CUTTING THE CREATURE DOWN.  Clint runs on.  The heroes confer over coms.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What do you want to do with this thing?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Get those stones as far away as possible!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No!  We need to send them back where they came from.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>There’s no way to send them back. Thanos destroyed our time machine.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hold on! (shrinking to normal size) That wasn’t our only time machine.  He clicks the KEYS TO LUIS’ VAN.  From a distance, we hear, “LA CUCARACHA.”  Steve immediately gets it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Does anyone see an ugly, brown van out there?  ABOVE, VALKYRIE SCANS THE FIELD FROM HER PEGASUS.  126   127</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Yeah.  But you’re not going to like where it’s parked.  LUIS’ VAN SITS SURROUNDED BY THOUSANDS OF ALIENS, DEEP BEHIND ENEMY LINES.  STEVE SURVEYS THE FIELD: AN ARMY STANDS BETWEEN THEM AND THE VAN, AIR AND GROUND CHOKED WITH ENEMIES.  TONY (INTO COM) Scott, how long do you need to get that thing working?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Uh, maybe ten minutes.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Get it started.  We’ll get the stones to you.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOPE VAN DYNE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>We’re on it, Cap.  SCOTT glances at her.  Cap?  THEY SHRINK DOWN AND FLY AWAY.  TONY FLIES UP TO DR. STRANGE, HOVERING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOPE VAN DYNE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Doc.  You said we win one in 14 million.  Is this how it goes down?  DR. STRANGE If I tell you what happens, it won’t happen.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You better be right.  Tony rockets away.  Strange coolly watches him go.  ACROSS THE FIELD...EBONY MAW RUSHES TO THANOS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>EBONY MAW</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sire, the stones!  THANOS TURNS TO SEE...CLINT FIGHTING THROUGH THE HORDE, CARRYING THE GAUNTLET.  A CULL HAMMERS CLINT, BUT THEN...T’CHALLA SLASHES THE CULL.  T’CHALLA Clint, give it to me.  127   128  CLINT HANDS THE GAUNTLET TO T’CHALLA, WHO TUCKS IT AND RUNS.  ACROSS THE FIELD...SCOTT AND HOPE FLY OVER A LONG PLATOON OF CHITAURI, TOWARD LUIS’ VAN.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>EBONY MAW</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(digging around) Ignition’s broken.  I’ll hotwire it-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HOPE VAN DYNE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Wait, you know how to do that?  Scott splices wires.  Sparks fly.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HOPE VAN DYNE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I was in prison.  I know how to do a lot of things.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>WANDA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You took everything from me.  Thanos takes THE BLADE off his back.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>WANDA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t even know who you are.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>WANDA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You will.  WANDA UNLEASHES A STORM OF RED ENERGY, HURLING WRECKAGE AT HIM.  AS THANOS FIGHTS HIS WAY THROUGH IT...  T’CHALLA DIVES FOR THE FALLEN GAUNTLET.  SUDDENLY...EBONY MAW MANIPULATES THE EARTH, PULLING THE GAUNTLET TOWARD HIM.  T’CHALLA WRAPS HIMSELF AROUND THE GLOVE, GETTING DRAGGED.  128   129  PETER PARKER (O.S.) I GOT IT!  T’CHALLA TURNS TO SEE PETER WHIZZING PAST.  HE HURLS THE GAUNTLET...THWIP!  Peter snatches it out of the air.  HE LANDS, ONLY TO FIND HIMSELF SURROUNDED BY OUTRIDERS.  PETER PARKER (CONT'D) Activate instant kill!  His robotic arms slash with expert precision.  ACROSS THE FIELD...WANDA LIFTS THANOS INTO THE AIR, RIPS HIS ARMOR OFF IN PIECES, THEN SLAMS HIM BACK TO THE GROUND.  Thanos groans, outmatched.  THANOS (INTO COM) Rain fire.  Wipe them all out.  CORVUS GLAIVE FIGHTS GROOT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CORVUS GLAIVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>WANDA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>But, sire, our troops-  THANOS (INTO COM) Just do it!  HIGH ABOVE...THE SANCTUARY-2 DESCENDS, CANNONS OPENING UP.  BELOW...WANDA looks up, raising a force field just as...  THE SANCTUARY-2 FIRES DOWN WITH EVERYTHING IT HAS.  SAKAARANS AND JABARI ALIKE GO FLYING AS EVERY SQUARE INCH GETS HIT.  THE BARRAGE HAMMERS THE RIVERBANK.  CRACKS FORM.  PEPPER CUTS DOWN AN ALIEN, THEN SPOTS SOMETHING OFF SCREEN.  PEPPER POTTS (INTO COM) Um, is anyone else seeing this?  TONY, SMART HULK, AND GAMORA turn to see...WATER GUSHING AS THE RIVERBANK THREATENS TO COLLAPSE.  SUDDENLY...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STRANGE AND WONG CONJURE TWO HUGE RUNE SHIELDS TO SHORE UP</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CORVUS GLAIVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>THE BANK.  MORE WIZARDS JOIN, CREATING A HUGE “RUNE LEVEE.”  THE SANCTUARY-2 MAINTAINS ITS BARRAGE.  ACROSS THE FIELD...STEVE spots PETER PARKER gradually being overwhelmed by Outriders.  129   130</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PETER PARKER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STRANGE AND WONG CONJURE TWO HUGE RUNE SHIELDS TO SHORE UP</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I got this...I got this...I don’t got this.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PETER PARKER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, Queens!  Heads up!  STEVE HURLS MJOLNIR OVER THE THRONG.  PETER WEBS ON...LETTING THE HAMMER PULL HIM OUT OF DANGER.  A MORTAR BLAST KNOCKS HIM OUT OF THE SKY, BUT PEPPER POTTS RESCUES HIM.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hang on, kid.  I’ve got you.  She drags him above the fray, then tosses him to...VALKYRIE FLYING PAST.  PETER PERCHES ATOP PEGASUS.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PETER PARKER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, nice to meet you-aaaaarg!  VALKYRIE SPURS INTO HIGH GEAR, DODGING CANNON FIRE... BUT NOT FAST ENOUGH.  A BLAST KNOCKS PETER TO THE GROUND.  HE GASPS, COVERED IN DEBRIS, STILL CLUTCHING THE GAUNTLET.  ALL AROUND THE FIELD, THE RELENTLESS BARRAGE PINS DOWN OUR HEROES.  ALL HOPE IS LOST.  Rocket and Groot dive for cover.  Groot wraps his branches around them both.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PETER PARKER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>At least we’re going out together this time...  SUDDENLY, EVERYTHING GOES SILENT.  ROCKET PEERS OUT FROM COVER TO SEE...THE CANNONS SWIVELING UP TOWARD THE CLOUDS.  SAM WILSON flies overhead.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What the hell is this?  TONY’S HUD: TONY FLIES OVERHEAD, SEARCHING UPWARD.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Friday, what are they firing at?  FRIDAY (O.S.) Something just entered the upper atmosphere.  130   131  Rocket looks up at...A COMET HEADING STRAIGHT FOR EARTH.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GROOT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>(nervous) I am Groot.  Rocket grins, knowing what’s coming.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GROOT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Just wait for it.  SUDDENLY, THE COMET VEERS...RIGHT TOWARD THE SHIP.  BOOM!  THE COMET TEARS THROUGH THE SANCTUARY-2, RIGHT OUT THE OTHER SIDE, REVEALING...CAROL DANVERS.  ROCKET (CONT'D) Oh, yeah!  CAROL GLOWS BRIGHTER AS SHE GOES BINARY, ROCKETING AGAIN THROUGH THE HULL.  BOOM!  THE SHIP LISTS, ENGINES EXPLODING.  CAROL EYES THE BATTLEFIELD, EXHAUSTED, LIGHT FADING.  STEVE (OVER COM) Danvers!  We’re gonna need an assist down here!  CAROL DANVERS (INTO COM) (under ragged breath) Roger...Rogers...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PETER PARKER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Uh, hey.  I’m Peter Parker.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CAROL DANVERS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PETER PARKER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, Peter Parker.  You got something for me?  131   132  Peter hands it over, staring out at the approaching horde.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PETER PARKER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CAROL DANVERS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t know how you’re gonna get it through all that-  WANDA (O.S.) Don’t worry, kid...  Peter turns to see...  WANDA, OKOYE, GAMORA, NEBULA, VALKYRIE, HOPE, AND SHURI WAITING.  Wanda’s hands begin to glow.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OKOYE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PETER PARKER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>She’s got help.  Carol glances at PEPPER and MANTIS, then tucks the gauntlet under her arm AND LEADS THEM OUT.  AT THE RIDGE...Thanos spots THE WOMEN OF MARVEL BLASTING THROUGH HIS TROOPS.  HE TRACKS THEIR PATH TO...THE VAN.  SCOTT KICKS THE REAR DOORS OPEN, EXPOSING THE QUANTUM TUNNEL.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SCOTT LANG</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OKOYE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thirty seconds!  Thanos understands immediately.  HE GRABS PROXIMA’S SPEAR FROM HER, AND STARTS RUNNING...  ACROSS THE FIELD...EBONY MAW SENDS WANDA TUMBLING, BUT SHURI BLASTS HIM OUT OF THE SKY.  CULL OBSIDIAN HAMMERS VALKYRIE, BUT NEBULA TAKES HIM OUT.  CAROL KEEPS GOING, GAUNTLET TUCKED UNDER HER ARM, GETTING CLOSER AND CLOSER TO...  THE VAN...WHERE THE QUANTUM TUNNEL BURSTS TO LIFE.  ACROSS THE FIELD...GROUNDED HEROES LOOK UP TO SEE CAROL NOW JUST YARDS AWAY FROM THE GOAL.  SHE PUTS HER HEAD DOWN, FLYING FOR ALL SHE’S WORTH.  BUT JUST AS SHE REACHES THE GAPING VAN DOORS...  THANOS THROWS THE SPEAR...  BOOM!  THE VAN EXPLODES, SENDING SCOTT AND CAROL FLYING, TAKING OUT SOME OF THE WIZARDS HOLDING BACK THE RIVER.  THANOS CATCHES PROXIMA’S RETURNING SPEAR.  132   133  TIME SLOWS AS...STEVE, THOR, AND TONY SPOT...THE GAUNTLET, LYING UNGUARDED IN THE DIRT.  The problem is...SO DOES THANOS.  TIME RESUMES AS...THEY ALL SCRAMBLE FOR THE STONES.  THEY COLLIDE.  THANOS SNATCHES UP THE GAUNTLET, KICKING THOR DOWN.  THANOS KNOCKS TONY ASIDE, THEN SQUEEZES THE CRUSHED GAUNTLET, POPPING IT OPEN...JUST WIDE ENOUGH TO PUT HIS HAND INSIDE.  STEVE LUNGES, BUT THANOS THROTTLES HIM.  FINALLY CLEAR, THANOS SLIPS ON THE GAUNTLET.  BUT BEFORE HE CAN SNAP...  CAROL ARRIVES.  SHE GRABS THE GLOVE, PREVENTING HIM FROM CLOSING HIS FIST.  HE HEADBUTTS HER...BUT SHE DOESN’T MOVE.  CAROL PRESSES THANOS DOWN, BUT BEFORE HE FALLS...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS PULLS THE POWER STONE FROM ITS HOUSING AND PUNCHES</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SCOTT LANG</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>CAROL, SENDING HER FLYING.  THE FIELD GOES QUIET.  NOW, NOTHING STANDS IN THANOS’ WAY.  Tony gets to his knees, realizing...  The Avengers are going to lose.  ACROSS THE FIELD...WATER STARTS TO SPILL INTO THE CRATER.  STRANGE TRIES TO HOLD IT BACK...BUT IT’S A LOSING BATTLE.  He looks to Tony...  Tony meets his eye.  And in that moment, all Strange can do is hold up a single finger.  “One.”  ACROSS THE FIELD...THANOS RETURNS THE POWER STONE TO THE GAUNTLET.  JUST AS THE ENERGY SURGES THROUGH HIM...  TONY LUNGES FOR THE GAUNTLET IN THANOS’ HAND, NANO-CLAMPING IT IN A VISE.  THANOS KNOCKS HIM ASIDE.  HE LIFTS HIS HAND IN THE AIR, TRIUMPHANT.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THANOS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS PULLS THE POWER STONE FROM ITS HOUSING AND PUNCHES</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I am...inevitable.  THANOS SNAPS HIS FINGERS.  But nothing happens.  Confused, Thanos turns the glove over to find...THE STONES ARE GONE.  He looks to see...TONY, NANO-PARTICLES SLIDING AND SHIFTING, FORMING A NEW GAUNTLET ON HIS OWN WRIST:  133   134  COMPLETE WITH SIX INFINITY STONES.  POWER SURGES THROUGH TONY, EXCRUCIATING, BUT HE STILL LIFTS HIS HAND...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>TONY</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THANOS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>And I...am Iron Man.  SNAP!  WHOOSH.  THE TIDAL WAVE EVAPORATES INTO MIST.  ALL AROUND THE FIELD, SAKAARANS AND OUTRIDERS FOLD IN ON THEMSELVES, ATOMS DISINTEGRATING.  THANOS LOOKS AROUND, WATCHING HIS TROOPS DISAPPEAR.  SHIPS VANISH FROM THE SKY.  CULLS, CHITAURI, ALL BLOW AWAY...  LEAVING THANOS STANDING ALONE.  AFTER A LONG MOMENT, HE SITS DOWN ON A ROCK...AND ACCEPTS HIS FATE.  He watches as...  HIS ATOMS DISSOLVE.  FINALLY, THANOS DISAPPEARS.  ACROSS THE FIELD, QUILL turns to GAMORA...BUT FINDS HER GONE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>TONY</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Babe?  Gamora?  ACROSS THE FIELD...TONY STARK FALLS BACK AGAINST THE UPTURNED ROOTS OF A TREE, ARMOR SMOKING, ARM WITHERED AND BLACKENED.  Dying.  RHODEY RUSHES TO HIM, BUT WITH ONE LOOK, HE KNOWS IT’S TOO LATE.  TONY EXHALES, ALMOST LETTING GO.  Then...  PETER PARKER lands, kneeling, taking Tony’s hand.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PETER PARKER</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Mr. Stark...Tony...it’s okay, it’s okay...Mr. Stark, we won.  You did it, sir...  But Tony gazes past him.  Rhodey puts his hand on Peter’s shoulder, guiding him away...  AS PEPPER ARRIVES.  She kneels, heartsick.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PETER PARKER</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, Friday, what’ve we got?  FRIDAY (O.S.) Life functions critical.  Pepper stares into her husband’s eyes...and knows.  134   (MORE)  135</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>PEPPER POTTS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Tony, look at me.  We’re going to be okay...  He stares at her, tears welling.  I’m sorry.  She touches his face, then leans in to kiss him.  PEPPER POTTS (CONT'D) You can rest now.  When she pulls back, she sees his eyes, fixed and glassy.  Everything goes quiet.  All around, OUR HEROES GATHER, the full weight of what’s happened dawning on them.  Tony Stark is gone.  FADE TO BLACK.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>CLINT BARTON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>PEPPER POTTS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I just wish there were some way I could let her know that we won. That we did it.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>WANDA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>CLINT BARTON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>She knows.  They both do.  Clint puts his arm around her.  They stare out at the water.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HAPPY HOGAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>WANDA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How are you doing, squirt?  You hungry?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HAPPY HOGAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Uh, huh.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HAPPY HOGAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What do you want?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HAPPY HOGAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Cheeseburgers?  Happy takes a beat, choked up.  Like father like daughter.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HAPPY HOGAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Did you know your dad liked cheeseburgers?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MORGAN STARK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HAPPY HOGAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No, I didn’t know that.  138   139</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>HAPPY HOGAN</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MORGAN STARK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m going to get you all the cheeseburgers you want.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>HAPPY HOGAN</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>So when can we expect you back?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>About that...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thor, your people need a king.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>They already have one.  And she’s a far better king than I could ever be.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Are you serious?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s time to be who I am, rather than who I’m supposed to be.  And a leader is who you are.  She processes this.  Does she want it?  She does.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You know, I’d make a lot of changes around here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m counting on it, Your Majesty.  Emotional, Val finally SHAKES HIS HAND.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>VALKYRIE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>What will you do?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>VALKYRIE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m not entirely sure.  For the first time in a thousand years, I have no path. (beat) But I do have a ride.  REVEAL...THE BENATAR parked behind them, Rocket alongside.  139   140</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Move it or lose it, Hairbag.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Home sweet home.  Tree!  Good to see you.  The Asgardians of the Galaxy, together again.  He settles beside Quill, who holomaps their course.  THOR (CONT'D) All right, where first?  He swipes through images on the screen.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You know, I’m still in charge, here, right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Of course.  Of course...  Thor swipes the map again.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>See, when you keep swiping my map, that sounds kind of like, “of course, I know you think you’re still in charge-”</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Quail, that’s your own insecurities bubbling up.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>DRAX</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You should fight one another for the honor of leadership.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>NEBULA</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>DRAX</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sounds fair.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>NEBULA</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s not necessary...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>ROCKET</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’ve got some blasters right here. Unless you want to use knives.  140   141</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>MANTIS</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>ROCKET</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Oh, yes, please, use knives-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>MANTIS</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>No one’s using knives!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>GROOT</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I am Groot!  Quill and Thor exchange nervous laughter.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>THOR</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>GROOT</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>There’ll be no knifing young Quail today.  Everyone knows who’s in charge.  A long awkward moment passes.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>QUILL</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>THOR</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Me. (sotto, to Thor) Right?  Thor just smiles...</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>QUILL</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Remember, you’ll have to return the stones to the exact moment they were taken.  Otherwise, we’re still looking at a whole bunch of nasty alternate realities.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Got it.  I’ll clip all the branches.  141   142  Steve takes the case.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You know, I tried.  When I had the gauntlet.  I really tried to bring her back. (beat) I miss her.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Me, too.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’d better get going.  We’re almost ready for you.  Steve and Sam approach the platform.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You look a little nervous going by yourself.  Ask nicely, I’ll go with you.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You’re a good man, Sam.  But this one’s on me.  When Steve reaches the platform, BUCKY stops him, pointed.  STEVE (CONT'D) Don’t do anything stupid ‘til I get back, okay?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BUCKY BARNES</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How can I?  You’re taking all the stupid with you.  Steve grins.  Bucky gives him a long hug.  BUCKY BARNES (CONT'D) Gonna miss you, buddy.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BUCKY BARNES</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It’s going to be okay, Buck.  Steve picks up Mjolnir and takes his place on the platform.  SAM LOOKS TO SMART HULK AT THE CONSOLE.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How long’s this gonna take?  142   143</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>For him, as long as he needs.  For us, five seconds. (calling out) Ready, Cap?  You’re good to go. Meet you right back here, okay?  Steve glances at Bucky as he answers.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You bet.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Going Quantum in three, two, one.  STEVE TAPS HIS CUFF AND SHRINKS TO NOTHING.  SMART HULK (CONT'D) Aaand, returning in five... four...three...two...one-  Silence.  Nothing happens.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where is he?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I don’t know.  He blew past our time stamp.  He should be here.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Get him back!</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m trying.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Get him the hell back-</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SMART HULK</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’M TRYING!  Just then...Bucky looks out to the water.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>BUCKY BARNES</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SMART HULK</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Sam.  Sam turns...  EXT AVENGERS COMPOUND, RIVERBANK - CONTINUOUS  Work crews have cleared a space overlooking the river. There, AN OLD MAN sits on a bench, staring out at the Hudson.  143   144  Move around him to find SAM watching from A FEW YARDS AWAY.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>BUCKY BARNES</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hey, Cap.  The man turns and we now see: STEVE ROGERS, age 112.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Hi, Sam.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Something go wrong...or something go right?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I thought, after everything that’s happened...maybe I should try out some of that life Tony always told me to get.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>How was it?  Steve looks at the river, 112 years of emotion in his face.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It was beautiful.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I’m happy for you.  Really.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thanks.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Only thing bumming me out is now I live in a world without Captain America.  Steve pulls up A CASE from beside him, giving it to Sam.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s kind of why I’m here.  Sam unzips it, revealing...A BRAND NEW SHIELD.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Where did you even get this?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>I had a little time to travel. (beat) Try it on.  144   145  Sam hesitates.  He glances back at Bucky, who nods.  Then Sam picks up the shield...and puts it on.  OLD STEVE (CONT'D) How does it feel?</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Like it’s someone else’s.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>It isn’t.  Sam tries to check his emotion.  He shakes Steve’s hand.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Thank you.  I’ll try my best.  Steve rests his other hand on Sam’s.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>That’s why it’s yours.  Sam smiles, noticing...STEVE’S TARNISHED WEDDING RING.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>SAM WILSON</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>OLD STEVE</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>You gonna tell me about her?  Steve smiles to himself at the end of a long, long life.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
	<SPEECH>
		<SPEAKER>OLD STEVE</SPEAKER>
		<RECEIVER>SAM WILSON</RECEIVER>
		<LINE>Nope.  I don’t think I will.  CUE MUSIC: “IT’S BEEN A LONG, LONG TIME,” HARRY JAMES.</LINE>
	</SPEECH>
</PLAY>
